<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- 

	Article
	
	$Id: fatherchoseyou.xml,v 1.1 2002/08/27 23:13:40 javajames27 Exp $
		
-->
<content title="Pastor's Pen - The Father Chose You">
	<article id="fatherchoseyou" image="homepage/pastors_pen.jpg">
	    <parts>
	      <part id="riches1">Last Week's "Pastor's Pen"</part>
	    </parts>
		<heading>Pastor Allen's Pen</heading>
		<title>The Father Chose You</title>
		<intro>Heavenly or earthly?  Earthly or heavenly?  We’re reminded that we live between two worlds.  One visible and the other invisible.  One material and the other spiritual.  In another place, Paul wrote the “our citizenship is in heaven” (Php  3:20).  In Joh 15:19, Jesus told His disciples, “You are not of the world, but I chose you out of the world.” Discover how the Father Chose You...</intro>
		<full>
			<p>
				<verse ref="Eph 1:3">Blessed be the God and Father of our Lord Jesus Christ, who has blessed us with every spiritual blessing in the heavenly places in Christ,</verse>
				<br/>
				<verse ref="Eph 1:4">just as He chose us in Him before the foundation of the world, that we should be holy and without blame before Him in love,</verse>
			</p>
			<p>Notice the words “blessed,” “blessed,” and “blessing” in verse 3.  What we have here is an adjective, verb, and noun respectively.  In the first case, we bless God by what we say.  In the second case, God blesses us by what He does.  But in the third case we have not just blessings but “spiritual” blessings and that in “heavenly places” or literally “in the heavenlies.”</p>
			<p>Heavenly or earthly?  Earthly or heavenly?  We’re reminded that we live between two worlds.  One visible and the other invisible.  One material and the other spiritual.  In another place, Paul wrote the “our citizenship is in heaven” (Php  3:20).  In Joh 15:19, Jesus told His disciples, “You are not of the world, but I chose you out of the world.” </p>
			<p>That phrase “spiritual blessing” could be translated “blessing of the Spirit” in which case we see the Trinity in verse 3.  Notice also the phrases “in Christ” (v. 3), “in Him” (v. 4), and “in the beloved” (v. 6).  That’s the key.  If you’re not “in Christ,” these things aren’t true about you.  But if you are, these things are true about you.  It says He “has blessed us” not “He will bless us.”  It also says “every spiritual blessing” not “some” or even “most.”  God has equipped, outfitted, and fully resourced every Christian!</p>
			<p>“The great newspaper publisher of the early part of this century, William Randolph Hearst, was a patron of art and spent a great deal of money collecting art treasures for his collection.  The story is told that one day he found a description of an artwork that he felt he must own, so he sent his agent abroad to find it.  After months of searching, the agent reported that he had found the treasured object and that it was close to home.  Where was it?  In Hearst’s warehouse, with many other treasures he owned that were still in their crates.  The great Hearst had been searching for a treasure he already owned!”<footnote-ref ref="1"/>   So it is with us.  </p>
			<p>Verse 4 brings us to what’s known as the doctrine of election.  There are few more controversial or contentious issues among Christians.  But in the next several paragraphs I’m going to resolve it once and for all.  Just kidding!  1Pe 1:2 says we were “elect according to the foreknowledge of God the Father.”  To “foreknow” means to know beforehand.  The Greek word is a compound.  The preposition means “before” and the verb means “to know.”  It’s not “fore-loved” but “forknew.”</p>
			<p>What does God know?  Everything!  Including “those who would receive Christ.”  Does that mean that “on the basis of this foreknowledge [God] elected [i.e. chose] them to salvation”?  Possibly.  But remember God is outside time. As Norman Geisler wrote, “All aspects of the eternal purpose of God are equally timeless<footnote-ref ref="2"/>.”   So on the one hand, foreknowledge might be said to have nothing more to do with election than election with foreknowledge.  And on the other hand, foreknowledge might be said to have as much to do with election as election with foreknowledge.</p>
			<p>It’s a mistake to think that if God chose, man doesn’t.  And it’s a mistake to think that if man chooses, God didn’t.  God chose for man to chose so that man’s exercise of responsibility in no way takes away from God’s exercise of sovereignty.  Don’t understand?  That’s okay.  I agree with John Stott: “Beware of any who try to systematize it too precisely or rigidly.” <footnote-ref ref="3"/> </p>
			<p>I remember attending a party as a teenager where we played a kissing game.  A girl picked a boy and led him into another room where, unknown to the rest of us, she gave him a kiss.  Then they came back together and he picked a girl and all three went into this other room where he gave her a kiss.  This continued until everyone at the party participated.  Now don’t go “church lady” on me!  There’s a point here!  It’s nice to be chosen!  Nice to be chosen sooner rather than later.  The last kid picked is still in therapy to this day!  </p>
			<p>One person could say, “God chose me.”  <br/>“He chose me, too!”<br/>“God chose me ‘before the foundation of the world.’  When did He choose you?”<br/>“He chose me ‘before the foundation of the world,’ too!”<br/>“Cool.”</p>
			<p>Charles Spurgeon said tongue in cheek, “If God hadn’t chosen me before the foundation of the world, He wouldn’t choose me now!”<footnote-ref ref="4"/>   The fact is God chose me when I was unholy and blame worthy. Later Paul writes, “that He might present her to Himself a glorious church, not having spot or wrinkle or any such thing, but that she should be holy and without blemish” (5:27).  That world “holy” is the same as “saints” (v. 1) and reminds us we’re set apart to someone.  That world “blameless” reminds us we’re set apart from something.</p>
			<p>Sometimes it helps to imagine a door.  On the frontside it says “whoever desires.”  When you walk through the door, the backside says chosen “in Him before the foundation of the world.”  I like the way J. Sidlow Baxter put it, “The elect are ‘whosoever will,’ and the non-elect are ‘whosoever won’t.’”<footnote-ref ref="5"/> </p>
			<p>“How do I know if I’m chosen?”<br/>Choose and you’ll discover you were chosen.<br/>“I don’t want to!”<br/>Then maybe you weren’t!</p>
			<p>For you to grow, there are things you must know about the Father.  First you must know that the Father chose you.</p>
			<footnotes>
			  <footnote id="1">  1500 Illustrations for Biblical Preaching, ed. Michael P. Green (Grand Rapids: Baker Books, 1989), p. 394.</footnote>
			  <footnote id="2">  Norman Geisler, Chosen But Free (Minneapolis, MN: Bethany House Publishers, 1999), p. 52.</footnote>
			  <footnote id="3">  John R. W. Stott, The Message of Ephesians (Downers Grove: Inter-Varsity Press, 1979), p. 37</footnote>
			  <footnote id="4">  Charles Spurgeon quoted in John Phillips, Exploring Ephesians (Neptune: Loizeaux Brothers, 1993), p. 32.</footnote>
			  <footnote id="5">  J. Sidlow Baxter, God So Loved (Grand Rapids: Zondervan Publishing House, 1960), p. 86.</footnote>
			</footnotes>
		</full>
	</article>
</content>
