<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- 

	Article
	
	$Id: riches1.xml,v 1.3 2002/07/11 13:47:20 javajames27 Exp $
		
-->
<content title="Pastor's Pen - How God has Enriched Us - Part 1">
	<article id="riches1" image="homepage/pastors_pen.jpg">
		<heading>Pastor Allen's Pen</heading>
		<title>How God has Enriched Us - Part 1</title>
		<intro>In the first three chapters of Ephesians, Paul used the words “rich” or “riches” six times.  I don’t want you to get the wrong idea.  Ephesians is a very practical book, as you’ll see in the last three chapters.  No doubt Paul wanted his readers to grow.  But he knew that for them to grow, there were things they must know.  In the first paragraph, Paul wrote about nine ways God has enriched us.  Three ways the Father has enriched us.  Four ways the Son has enriched us.  And two ways the Holy Spirit has enriched us.  Read these verses and you can come to only one conclusion, “I’m rich!”</intro>
		<full>
			<p>Recently a twenty-year-old woman walked into an Atlanta-area convenience store and bought ten lottery tickets.  She was a 	first time player lured by a multimillion-dollar jackpot.  Hours later Erika Greene learned she’d won $58.9 million dollars.  That’s about 	$34 	million after	taxes!  “I just shook and shook,” Greene said.  “Actually, I was kind of stunned.  I didn’t have anything to say.”  The 	next day she and several others stopped by the convenience store where she’d bought the ticket.  A witness said, “They were in a 	pretty good 	mood.”  Well I guess so!</p>
			<p>In the first three chapters of Ephesians, Paul used the words “rich” or “riches” six times.  I don’t want you to get the wrong idea. Ephesians is a very practical book, as you’ll see in the last three chapters.  No doubt Paul wanted his readers to grow.  But he knew that for them to grow, there were things they must know.  In the first paragraph, Paul wrote about nine ways God has enriched us.  Three ways the Father has enriched us.  Four ways the Son has enriched us.  And two ways the Holy Spirit has enriched us.  Read these verses and you can come to only one conclusion, “I’m rich!”</p>
			<p>But I’m getting ahead of myself.  Before we look in this first chapter at ways the Father has enriched us, let’s break down the 		introduction.</p>
			<subheading>Introduction</subheading>
			<p>
				<verse ref="Eph 1:1">Paul, an apostle of Jesus Christ by the will of God, To the saints who are in Ephesus, and faithful in Christ Jesus:</verse>
				<br/>
				<verse ref="Eph 1:2">Grace to you and peace from God our Father and the Lord Jesus Christ.</verse>
			</p>
			<p>When we think of Paul, we think of the three journeys he took planting churches throughout the Roman Empire.  We think of the 	thirteen 	New Testament books he wrote (fourteen if you include Hebrews).  And we think of the threats.  Threats?  On a recent flight 	from Europe I saw a guy wearing a T-shirt that said “So many right wing Christians – so few lions.”  I couldn’t believe it!  Before he 	was a Christian, Paul was known as Saul and he would have loved that shirt.  He terrorized Christians right up until he came to know 	Christ as recorded in Acts 9.</p>
			<p>We know whom this book – letter really – was from.  Who was it to?  Paul wrote to saints.  Saints?  “I thought you had to be dead to be a saint!  I thought you had to have done miracles!  That rules me out.  I’m not dead.  And I know more about Miracle Whip than I do about miracles!”  But wait.  The word saint just means “set apart.”  Every Christian is a saint.  I place my faith in Christ and He sets me apart for Himself.  Call me “Saint Allen.”  Or not!  But you’re a saint, too, if you’re a Christian.</p>
			<p>These saints lived in Ephesus on the West coast of Asia Minor (modern Turkey).  As many as half a million people may have lived there at that time.  Ephesus was a capital city.  It was a marketplace player.  And it was a center of spirituality.  Come to think of it, Ephesus was a lot like Austin, the city where I pastor.  Paul visited while on his second journey but spent several years there on his third.  Now perhaps ten years later, he’s writing to them.</p>
			<p>Paul greeted his readers with words familiar to all of them.  “Grace” and “peace” were the common Greek and Hebrew greetings respectively.  It was as if Paul began, “Wazzzzup!”  But for Paul this was more than a marketplace greeting.  This was an affirmation of faith.  He knew by experience that everyone receives God’s grace receives His peace.  With that Paul wrote about three ways the Father has enriched us.</p>
		</full>
	</article>
</content>
