<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- 

	Article
	
	$Id: secretsuccess3.xml,v 1.1 2002/04/02 04:10:10 javajames27 Exp $
		
-->
<content title="Featured Article" base="..">
	  <article id="secretsuccess3">
	    <parts>
	      <part id="secretsuccess1"/>
	      <part id="secretsuccess2"/>
	    </parts>
	    <heading>Pastor Allen's Pen</heading>
	    <title>The Secret to Spiritual Success Part 3</title>
	    <intro>Jesus said, "If anyone does not abide in Me, he is cast out as a branch and is withered; and they gather them and throw them into the fire, and they are burned" (v. 6). People want to know if this verse teaches that a Christian can lose their salvation.</intro>
	    <full><p>Jesus said, "If anyone does not abide in Me, he is cast out as a branch and is withered; and they gather them and throw them into the fire, and they are burned" (v. 6). People want to know if this verse teaches that a Christian can lose their salvation. I must say that it is difficult for me to understand how a person who was genuinely born again could ever lose their salvation. But I must also say that I have no intention of finding out! While others argue and debate, we would do well to stay so close to the Lord that it is never an issue for us. This verse certainly does highlight the tragedy of having a saved soul and a wasted life. You can go into any furniture store you like and you will be hard pressed to find anything made with grapevine wood! It is useless. The dead vines that were trimmed in the winter were burned during cold nights in the spring to keep the frost from killing the new growth. The emphasis here is on the uselessness of fruitlessness. I like the words of Warren Wiersbe, </p>
         <p>"We must remember that this fruit is produced to be eaten, not to be admired and put on display. People around us are starving for love, joy, peace, and all the other graces of the Spirit. When they find them in our lives [or in our church I might add], they know that we have something they lack. We do not bear fruit for our own consumption; we bear fruit that others might be fed and helped, and that Christ might be glorified." </p>
         <p>No fruit? Fruit? More fruit? Much fruit? Where are you now? Where would you like to be a year from now? Do you have a personal strategy for spiritual success? Are you determined, with God's help, to be a spiritual success? Only Christians can abide in Christ and thus succeed spiritually. Have you given your life to Christ? I'd like to close with the story of young man known as Wrong-way Roy. Maybe you've heard of him. His actual name was Roy Riegels, and he played in the Rose Bowl of 1929. It was California against Georgia Tech. Roy was the All-American Center from California. He was so talented he played both offense and defense. </p>
          <p>It was near the end of the first half when a Tech player fumbled the ball. Roy scooped and up the ball and ran as fast as he could toward the end zone. There was only one problem. In all the excitement, Roy had become disoriented and was running toward the wrong end zone! Centers are not usually the fastest men on the team and one of Roy's teammates ran after him and tackled him just before he crossed the wrong goal line. Minutes later his team was forced to punt from the end zone. The punt was blocked resulting in a safety, and two points, for Georgia Tech. At halftime, you can imagine how Roy must have felt. California's coach was usually very animated and vocal in the locker room but he did not say a word. The only sound was that of the All-American, sitting in the corner with his towel over his head crying. A referee informed the team that there were only three minutes before the second half started. Finally, the coach stood and announced to the team, "Men, the same team that started the first half will start the second half. </p>
          <p>"Roy Riegels lifted his head. His eyes were red, and his cheeks were wet with tears. "Coach, I can't do it. I've ruined you. I've ruined the University. I've ruined myself. I couldn't face that crowd in the stadium to save my life." The coach reached out his hand and said, "Roy, get up and go on back; the game is only half over." It is said that Roy Riegels went on to play one of the most inspiring second halves in Rose Bowl history. </p>
          <p>Maybe you feel like anything but a spiritual success. Maybe you feel like a failure. But I believe that the Lord would put His arm around you and say, "Get up and go on back; the game is only half over." With His mercy, grace, and forgiveness there is always the opportunity for us to start over, to be a spiritual success </p>
	    </full>
	  </article>
</content>
