<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- 

	What's New
	
	$Id: whatsnew.xml,v 1.29 2003/04/04 21:29:39 javajames27 Exp $
		
-->
<content title="What's New" base=".">
	<news>
		<news-item id="29" date="20030430" expires="20030430" showOnHomepage="true">
			<logo align="right" img="../images/YEV02a.jpg" alt="Year End Video"/>
			<title>2002 Year End Video</title>
			<detail>Check out the <link href="http://www.calvarychapel.org/austin/video/2002yeva.ram">Year End Video</link> with your <link href="http://www.real.com">RealVideo</link> player!</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="30" date="20030430" expires="20030430" showOnHomepage="true">
			<logo align="right" img="../images/YEV02b.jpg" alt="Year In Review Video"/>
			<title>2002 Year In Review Video</title>
			<detail>Check out the <link href="http://www.calvarychapel.org/austin/video/2002yevb.ram">Year In Review Video</link> with your <link href="http://www.real.com">RealVideo</link> player!</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="31" date="20030401" expires="20030401" showOnHomepage="false">
			<title>Marriage Ministry</title>
			<detail>The Spring group meetings begin this week. If you signed up, your books will be available at the first meeting. <link href="../ministries/marriage.html">Learn more...</link>
			</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="32" date="20030201" expires="20030315" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Children's Ministry</title>
			<detail>Several volunteer positions are open on Sunday and Wednesday.  Please check the Calvary Kids Hallway board for more info. It is very important to pick up, at various places in the lobby, a schedule of training sessions if you've signed up.  There are sessions Apr 6, during the 2nd or 3rd services and also on Apr 13.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="33" date="20030301" expires="20030319" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Stop and Seek</title>
			<detail>Please join us this Wednesday evening, Mar 19, at 7PM, as Pastor Allen leads us in the last of four special services devoted to prayer and waiting for a word from the Lord for each of us, our families and our church.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="34" date="20030301" expires="20030319" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Calvary Bookstore </title>
			<detail>Several volunteer positions are open on Sundays and Wednesdays.  Please contact Andrea Rigg at the church office (719.4667) or come by the bookstore for more information.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="35" date="20030301" expires="20030401" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Children's Ministry Sign In</title>
			<detail>The new sign in system will begin April 6.  Pick up a flyer and a form to be filled out in the Children's Ministry area today.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="36" date="20030301" expires="20030327" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Men's Ministry</title>
			<detail>Starting Tuesday the men’s bible study will meet every Tuesday night until the end of May.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="37" date="20030320" expires="20030418" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>New Home Fellowship</title>
			<detail>A new home group will start meeting on Friday, Apr 11, at 7:30PM in Cedar Park.  It will be lead by James Lozano and hosted by James and Talinda Higginbotham (1800 Nelson Ranch Loop).  Flyers with directions are available in the lobby.  Contact the Higginbotham's (336.8493) for more information.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="38" date="20030320" expires="20030418" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Young Disciples Club</title>
			<detail>“YDC” is a discipleship club for Wise Guys, Witnesses and Watchmen--boys and girls K-5th grade.  There is worship, Bible, game and group times each Wednesday evening.  Pick up a YDC flyer at the Octopus in the lobby for more information.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="39" date="20030406" expires="20030406" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Daylight Saving Time</title>
			<detail>Next Sunday, April 6, is the time to “spring forward” by setting clocks ahead 1 hour Saturday night.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="40" date="20030403" expires="20030406" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Leander Home Fellowship</title>
			<detail>The Leander Home Fellowship has a new meeting location.  For more information, call Robert and Sandra Verastegui (259.0251).</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="41" date="20030404" expires="20030501" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>God Bless Our Military Serving in Iraq</title>
			<detail>We want to pray for all those who are serving and their families.  We want to pray especially for our own Calvary families.  If you are a member of one of those families or know of one, please call the office (719-4667) so we may pray for them by name!</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="42" date="20030404" expires="20030501" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Bookstore</title>
			<detail>Want to grow deeper in your walk with the Lord?  There's something for everyone in the family including great music, journals, and books for kids.  If you can't find what you're looking for, we can order it for you.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="43" date="20030301" expires="20030501" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Internet Ministry</title>
			<detail>Want to grow deeper in your walk with the Lord by serving?  <link href="mailto:webservant-austin@calvarychapel.org">Contact the web ministry</link> if you have skills in any of the following areas: Java, JSP, XML, Javascript, HTML, and professional web design. </detail>
		</news-item>
	</news>
</content>
