<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- 

	What's New
	
	$Id: whatsnew.xml,v 1.39 2003/07/11 20:37:03 javajames27 Exp $
		
-->
<content title="What's New" base=".">
	<news>
		<news-item id="29" date="20030430" expires="20030430" showOnHomepage="true">
			<logo align="right" img="../images/YEV02a.jpg" alt="Year End Video"/>
			<title>2002 Year End Video</title>
			<detail>Check out the <link href="http://www.calvarychapel.org/austin/video/2002yeva.ram">Year End Video</link> with your <link href="http://www.real.com">RealVideo</link> player!</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="30" date="20030430" expires="20030430" showOnHomepage="true">
			<logo align="right" img="../images/YEV02b.jpg" alt="Year In Review Video"/>
			<title>2002 Year In Review Video</title>
			<detail>Check out the <link href="http://www.calvarychapel.org/austin/video/2002yevb.ram">Year In Review Video</link> with your <link href="http://www.real.com">RealVideo</link> player!</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="31" date="20030401" expires="20030401" showOnHomepage="false">
			<title>Marriage Ministry</title>
			<detail>The Spring group meetings begin this week. If you signed up, your books will be available at the first meeting. <link href="../ministries/marriage.html">Learn more...</link>
			</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="32" date="20030201" expires="20030315" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Children's Ministry</title>
			<detail>Several volunteer positions are open on Sunday and Wednesday.  Please check the Calvary Kids Hallway board for more info. It is very important to pick up, at various places in the lobby, a schedule of training sessions if you've signed up.  There are sessions Apr 6, during the 2nd or 3rd services and also on Apr 13.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="33" date="20030301" expires="20030319" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Stop and Seek</title>
			<detail>Please join us this Wednesday evening, Mar 19, at 7PM, as Pastor Allen leads us in the last of four special services devoted to prayer and waiting for a word from the Lord for each of us, our families and our church.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="34" date="20030301" expires="20030319" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Calvary Bookstore </title>
			<detail>Several volunteer positions are open on Sundays and Wednesdays.  Please contact Andrea Rigg at the church office (719.4667) or come by the bookstore for more information.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="35" date="20030301" expires="20030401" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Children's Ministry Sign In</title>
			<detail>The new sign in system will begin April 6.  Pick up a flyer and a form to be filled out in the Children's Ministry area today.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="36" date="20030301" expires="20030327" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Men's Ministry</title>
			<detail>Starting Tuesday the men’s bible study will meet every Tuesday night until the end of May.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="37" date="20030320" expires="20030418" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>New Home Fellowship</title>
			<detail>A new home group will start meeting on Friday, Apr 11, at 7:30PM in Cedar Park.  It will be lead by James Lozano and hosted by James and Talinda Higginbotham (1800 Nelson Ranch Loop).  Flyers with directions are available in the lobby.  Contact the Higginbotham's (336.8493) for more information.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="38" date="20030320" expires="20030418" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Young Disciples Club</title>
			<detail>“YDC” is a discipleship club for Wise Guys, Witnesses and Watchmen--boys and girls K-5th grade.  There is worship, Bible, game and group times each Wednesday evening.  Pick up a YDC flyer at the Octopus in the lobby for more information.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="39" date="20030406" expires="20030406" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Daylight Saving Time</title>
			<detail>Next Sunday, April 6, is the time to “spring forward” by setting clocks ahead 1 hour Saturday night.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="40" date="20030403" expires="20030406" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Leander Home Fellowship</title>
			<detail>The Leander Home Fellowship has a new meeting location.  For more information, call Robert and Sandra Verastegui (259.0251).</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="41" date="20030301" expires="20030501" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>God Bless Our Military Serving in Iraq</title>
			<detail>We want to pray for all those who are serving and their families.  We want to pray especially for our own Calvary families.  If you are a member of one of those families or know of one, please call the office (719-4667) so we may pray for them by name!</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="42" date="20030404" expires="20030501" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Bookstore</title>
			<detail>Want to grow deeper in your walk with the Lord?  There's something for everyone in the family including great music, journals, and books for kids.  If you can't find what you're looking for, we can order it for you.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="43" date="20030302" expires="20030601" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Release Your Inner Geek</title>
			<detail>The gospel presented in multimedia - from streaming video/audio to web servers, networking, and programming. Join the Internet Ministry as we take God's Word to the world and serve the body of Calvary Austin! Join in the fun and serve the Lord with your skills. <link href="mailto:webservant-austin@calvarychapel.org">Contact the web ministry</link> or visit the <link href="../ministries/internet.html">Internet Ministry Page</link> to learn how you can be a part of this exciting outreach.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="44" date="20030402" expires="20030601" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Women's Ministry</title>
			<detail>Our Women¹s Ministry is offering 2 studies, Jun 3 through Aug 12. A bible study titled "Healed and Set Free" will meet every Tuesday, 7-9PM. Sharing will be in very small groups.  And a study titled "Principles for Women in Leadership", designed for those desiring to know more about women¹s leadership will meet every other Tuesday, 7-9PM. Sign up at the Events Center. 
</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="45" date="20030418" expires="20030425" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Women's Retreat Tapes</title>
			<detail>Audio tapes from the women’s retreat are now available.  Place your order at the Media Center in the lobby.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="46" date="20030511" expires="20030530" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Frontline Worship CD</title>
			<detail>Gracemongers, one of the FrontLine Worship teams has released their CD.  It is available in the bookstore for $10.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="47" date="20030511" expires="20030602" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Free Indeed Addictions Ministry</title>
			<detail>Calvary Austin is introducing a new internet-based ministry to address pornography, substance abuse, overeating, smoking or other addictions.  If you need help in one of these areas or would like to serve in this ministry visit the <link href="../ministries/freeindeed.html">ministry's home page</link></detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="48" date="20030511" expires="20030602" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>The Cupboard</title>
			<detail>Our food pantry provides food to families in the body of Calvary during times of need.  If you need assistance from this ministry, contact the church office. 
</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="49" date="20030518" expires="20030713" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Children's Conference Hosting</title>
			<detail>Would you like to bless one or more peope attending our CM Conference from out of town with accommodations in your home?  If interested, sign up to be a host family at the Events Center. 
</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="50" date="20030522" expires="20030714" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Crown Financial Ministry</title>
			<detail>There are still some spaces left for the course on handling money God's way.  Sign up at the Events Center today.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="51" date="20030522" expires="20030713" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Bookstore</title>
			<detail>Want to grow deeper in your walk with the Lord?  Stop and check-out all the Bibles, books, study guides and CDs.  Open after every Wednesday &amp; Sunday service.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="52" date="20030529" expires="20030713" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Fan Drive</title>
			<detail>Calvary Singles is sponsoring the 3rd annual fan drive for Eldercare.  Purchase a fan and drop it off in our new collection area in the back hall.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<!--
		<news-item id="53" date="20030529" expires="20030616" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Calvary T-Shirt Blowout Sale</title>
			<detail>Want to wear a Calvary t-shirt to the Baptism/Picnic?  Visit the bookstore and purchase one for only $3.00. Choose from many children¹s sizes.  A few adult sizes remain.</detail>
		</news-item>
		-->
		<news-item id="54" date="20030703" expires="20030729" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Seasoned Saints Fellowship</title>
			<detail>A new ministry has started.  Seasoned Saints is for those special folks in our church who, by the grace of God, have been a part of this world for a good spell longer than most others and have so much to offer by their presence.  We¹ll meet at the church the 1st Sunday of each month starting tonight, July 6, at 5PM for fellowship.  Pick up a flyer at the Info Center or call for more information</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="55" date="20030704" expires="20030729" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Lunch with Calvary Continuum</title>
			<detail>Calvary Continuum, on 590AM KIXL, has moved to 12:00pm and 7:30pm every weekday. Spend your lunch break listening to Allen's message</detail>
		</news-item>

	</news>
</content>
