<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- 

	What's New
	
	$Id: whatsnew.xml,v 1.52 2003/10/27 06:28:11 gregk Exp $
		
-->
<content title="What's New" base=".">
	<news>
		<news-item id="29" date="20030430" expires="20030430" showOnHomepage="true">
			<logo align="right" img="../images/YEV02a.jpg" alt="Year End Video"/>
			<title>2002 Year End Video</title>
			<detail>Check out the <link href="http://www.calvarychapel.org/austin/video/2002yeva.ram">Year End Video</link> with your <link href="http://www.real.com">RealVideo</link> player!</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="30" date="20030430" expires="20030430" showOnHomepage="true">
			<logo align="right" img="../images/YEV02b.jpg" alt="Year In Review Video"/>
			<title>2002 Year In Review Video</title>
			<detail>Check out the <link href="http://www.calvarychapel.org/austin/video/2002yevb.ram">Year In Review Video</link> with your <link href="http://www.real.com">RealVideo</link> player!</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="31" date="20030401" expires="20030401" showOnHomepage="false">
			<title>Marriage Ministry</title>
			<detail>The Spring group meetings begin this week. If you signed up, your books will be available at the first meeting. <link href="../ministries/marriage.html">Learn more...</link>
			</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="32" date="20030201" expires="20030315" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Children's Ministry</title>
			<detail>Several volunteer positions are open on Sunday and Wednesday.  Please check the Calvary Kids Hallway board for more info. It is very important to pick up, at various places in the lobby, a schedule of training sessions if you've signed up.  There are sessions Apr 6, during the 2nd or 3rd services and also on Apr 13.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="33" date="20030301" expires="20030319" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Stop and Seek</title>
			<detail>Please join us this Wednesday evening, Mar 19, at 7PM, as Pastor Allen leads us in the last of four special services devoted to prayer and waiting for a word from the Lord for each of us, our families and our church.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="34" date="20030301" expires="20030319" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Calvary Bookstore </title>
			<detail>Several volunteer positions are open on Sundays and Wednesdays.  Please contact Andrea Rigg at the church office (719.4667) or come by the bookstore for more information.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="35" date="20030301" expires="20030401" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Children's Ministry Sign In</title>
			<detail>The new sign in system will begin April 6.  Pick up a flyer and a form to be filled out in the Children's Ministry area today.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="36" date="20030301" expires="20030327" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Men's Ministry</title>
			<detail>Starting Tuesday the men’s bible study will meet every Tuesday night until the end of May.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="37" date="20030320" expires="20030418" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>New Home Fellowship</title>
			<detail>A new home group will start meeting on Friday, Apr 11, at 7:30PM in Cedar Park.  It will be lead by James Lozano and hosted by James and Talinda Higginbotham (1800 Nelson Ranch Loop).  Flyers with directions are available in the lobby.  Contact the Higginbotham's (336.8493) for more information.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="38" date="20030320" expires="20030418" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Young Disciples Club</title>
			<detail>“YDC” is a discipleship club for Wise Guys, Witnesses and Watchmen--boys and girls K-5th grade.  There is worship, Bible, game and group times each Wednesday evening.  Pick up a YDC flyer at the Octopus in the lobby for more information.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="39" date="20030406" expires="20030406" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Daylight Saving Time</title>
			<detail>Next Sunday, April 6, is the time to “spring forward” by setting clocks ahead 1 hour Saturday night.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="40" date="20030403" expires="20030406" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Leander Home Fellowship</title>
			<detail>The Leander Home Fellowship has a new meeting location.  For more information, call Robert and Sandra Verastegui (259.0251).</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="41" date="20030301" expires="20030501" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>God Bless Our Military Serving in Iraq</title>
			<detail>We want to pray for all those who are serving and their families.  We want to pray especially for our own Calvary families.  If you are a member of one of those families or know of one, please call the office (719-4667) so we may pray for them by name!</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="42" date="20030404" expires="20030501" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Bookstore</title>
			<detail>Want to grow deeper in your walk with the Lord?  There's something for everyone in the family including great music, journals, and books for kids.  If you can't find what you're looking for, we can order it for you.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="43" date="20030302" expires="20030601" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Release Your Inner Geek</title>
			<detail>The gospel presented in multimedia - from streaming video/audio to web servers, networking, and programming. Join the Internet Ministry as we take God's Word to the world and serve the body of Calvary Austin! Join in the fun and serve the Lord with your skills. <link href="mailto:webservant-austin@calvarychapel.org">Contact the web ministry</link> or visit the <link href="../ministries/internet.html">Internet Ministry Page</link> to learn how you can be a part of this exciting outreach.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="44" date="20030402" expires="20030601" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Women's Ministry</title>
			<detail>Our Women¹s Ministry is offering 2 studies, Jun 3 through Aug 12. A bible study titled "Healed and Set Free" will meet every Tuesday, 7-9PM. Sharing will be in very small groups.  And a study titled "Principles for Women in Leadership", designed for those desiring to know more about women¹s leadership will meet every other Tuesday, 7-9PM. Sign up at the Events Center. 
</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="45" date="20030418" expires="20030425" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Women's Retreat Tapes</title>
			<detail>Audio tapes from the women’s retreat are now available.  Place your order at the Media Center in the lobby.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="46" date="20030511" expires="20030530" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Frontline Worship CD</title>
			<detail>Gracemongers, one of the FrontLine Worship teams has released their CD.  It is available in the bookstore for $10.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="47" date="20030511" expires="20030602" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Free Indeed Addictions Ministry</title>
			<detail>Calvary Austin is introducing a new internet-based ministry to address pornography, substance abuse, overeating, smoking or other addictions.  If you need help in one of these areas or would like to serve in this ministry visit the <link href="../ministries/freeindeed.html">ministry's home page</link></detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="48" date="20030511" expires="20030602" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>The Cupboard</title>
			<detail>Our food pantry provides food to families in the body of Calvary during times of need.  If you need assistance from this ministry, contact the church office. 
</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="49" date="20030518" expires="20030713" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Children's Conference Hosting</title>
			<detail>Would you like to bless one or more peope attending our CM Conference from out of town with accommodations in your home?  If interested, sign up to be a host family at the Events Center. 
</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="50" date="20030522" expires="20030714" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Crown Financial Ministry</title>
			<detail>There are still some spaces left for the course on handling money God's way.  Sign up at the Events Center today.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="51" date="20030522" expires="20030712" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Bookstore</title>
			<detail>Want to grow deeper in your walk with the Lord?  Stop and check-out all the Bibles, books, study guides and CDs.  Open after every Wednesday and Sunday service.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="52" date="20030529" expires="20030720" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Fan Drive</title>
			<detail>Calvary Singles is sponsoring the 3rd annual fan drive for Eldercare.  Purchase a fan and drop it off in our new Collection Area in the hall near the restroom.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<!--
		<news-item id="53" date="20030529" expires="20030616" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Calvary T-Shirt Blowout Sale</title>
			<detail>Want to wear a Calvary t-shirt to the Baptism/Picnic?  Visit the bookstore and purchase one for only $3.00. Choose from many children¹s sizes.  A few adult sizes remain.</detail>
		</news-item>
		-->
		<news-item id="54" date="20030703" expires="20030729" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Seasoned Saints Fellowship</title>
			<detail>A new ministry has started.  Seasoned Saints is for those special folks in our church who, by the grace of God, have been a part of this world for a good spell longer than most others and have so much to offer by their presence.  We'll meet at the church the 1st Sunday of each month starting July 6, at 5PM for fellowship.  Pick up a flyer at the Info Center or call for more information</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="55" date="20030704" expires="20030712" showOnHomepage="false">
			<title>Lunch with Calvary Continuum</title>
			<detail>Calvary Continuum, on 590AM KIXL, has moved to 12:00pm and 7:30pm every weekday. Spend your lunch break listening to Allen's message</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="56" date="20030712" expires="20030828" showOnHomepage="false">
			<title>Worshippers Wanted!!</title>
			<detail>Participate in the "live" recording of our first worship CD. The recording will take place over two evenings, Aug 26 and 27 beginning at 7PM. Come sing and be a part of this worship experience. Childcare will be provided on Tues for ages 2 years through 5th grade.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="57" date="20030712" expires="20030927" showOnHomepage="false">
			<title>Men's Retreat</title>
			<detail>Registration continues until Aug 31th for the Sept 25-27 retreat at T-Bar-M Ranch in New Braunfels. The main speaker is Ken Graves from Calvary Chapel Bangor, Maine. Sign up at the Events Center.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="58" date="20030712" expires="20030930" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Prayer Chain</title>
			<detail>Members of the body of Calvary are encouraged to contact the Prayer Chain with prayer needs so those who are a part of the ministry may lift them up to the Lord (479-9454).</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="59" date="20030712" expires="20030720" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>The Cupboard</title>
			<detail>Our food pantry will provide food to families in the body of Calvary during times of need. You may donate non-perishable food and personal hygiene items. Place donations in the Collection Area near the restrooms. If you need assistance from this ministry, contact the church office. For more information contact Derrick or Crystal Kinney (310-2590).</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="60" date="20030712" expires="20030720" showOnHomepage="false">
			<title>Bookstore</title>
			<detail>Check-out all the Bibles, books, study guides, journals, and books for kids. You can also special order. The bookstore is open after every Wednesday and Sunday service.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="61" date="20030712" expires="20030720" showOnHomepage="false">
			<title>Audio</title>
			<detail>Pastor Allen's messages are available on tape, CD, and MP3 after every service in the lobby. Tape catalogs are also available.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="62" date="20030712" expires="20030720" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Radio, TV and Internet</title>
			<detail>Hear Pastor Allen on Calvary Continuum at NOON and 7:30PM on KIXL 970AM or watch our television program on cable access channel 11 Saturdays at NOON. Watch select services live on the internet or check out the audio archive on our web site.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="63" date="20030809" expires="20030831" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>School of Ministry</title>
			<detail>Interested in learning more about apologetics, theology, church history, small group ministry, evangelism or inductive Bible study? We are taking signups until Aug 31th at the Events Center. School of Ministry begins Sept 8th and meets on Wednesdays at 7PM at the church.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="64" date="20030809" expires="20030829" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Scholarships Needed</title>
			<detail>If you would like to give a partial or full scholarship for a poor college student to attend the 2003 Mid-South College and Career Retreat on Labor Day weekend, go by the Events Center.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="65" date="20030810" expires="20030816" showOnHomepage="false">
			<title>Bookstore</title>
			<detail>Check-out all the Bibles, books, study guides, journals, and books for kids. You can also special order. The bookstore is open after every Wednesday and Sunday service.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="66" date="20030810" expires="20030816" showOnHomepage="false">
			<title>Audio</title>
			<detail>Pastor Allen's messages are available on tape, CD, and MP3 after every service in the lobby. Tape catalogs are also available.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="67" date="20030810" expires="20030812" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Radio, TV and Internet</title>
			<detail>Hear Pastor Allen on Calvary Continuum at NOON and 7:30PM on KIXL 970AM or watch our television program on cable access channel 11 Saturdays at NOON. Watch select services live on the internet or check out the audio archive on our web site.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="68" date="20030824" expires="20030912" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Preorder Your "Live" Worship CD!</title>
			<detail>You may support our recording project by preordering the Calvary Austin Worship CD at a 20% discount for $12. Come by the Events Center today.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="69" date="20030824" expires="20030912" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>New Believers' Class</title>
			<detail>The 12-week class in basic Bible fundamentals meets on Mondays at 7PM in the New Parents room starting Sept 8th. Sign up at the Events Center.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="70" date="20030824" expires="20030923" showOnHomepage="false">
			<title>Women's Fall Bible Studies</title>
			<detail>Sign up at the Events Center for the "Face-to-Face with Women of the Bible" study. The costs is $13. The Tuesday Morning Study will begin Sept 23rd, meet at 10AM, and provide cooperative childcare. The Tuesday Evening Study will begin Sept 16th, meet every other Tuesday at 7PM, and will not provide childcare.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="71" date="20030825" expires="20030925" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Radio, TV and Internet</title>
			<detail>Hear Pastor Allen on Calvary Continuum at NOON on KIXL 970AM or at 9:30AM on 1010AM. Watch our television program on cable access channel 11 Saturdays at NOON. Watch select services live on the internet or check out the audio archive on our web site.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="72" date="20030825" expires="20030916" showOnHomepage="false">
			<title>Audio</title>
			<detail>Pastor Allen's messages are available on tape, CD, and MP3 after every service in the lobby. Tape catalogs are also available.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="73" date="20030825" expires="20030930" showOnHomepage="false">
			<title>Bookstore</title>
			<detail>Check-out our large selection of books. You can also special order. The bookstore is open after every Wednesday and Sunday service.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="74" date="20030905" expires="20030923" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Toddler Teacher Needed</title>
			<detail>The Women's Tuesday Morning Bible Study is in need of a paid teacher to teach the toddlers(ages 10 - 35 months) while their moms attend the study. The hours are from 9:40 AM to 11:40 AM starting Sept 23rd. If yor are interested in the position, please contact Vicky Lozano at 336-8368.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="75" date="20030905" expires="20031010" showOnHomepage="false">
			<title>The Cupboard</title>
			<detail>Our food pantry will provide food to families in the body of Calvary during times of need. You may donate non-perishable food and personal hygiene items. Place donations in the Collection Area near the restrooms. If you need assistance from this ministry, contact the church office. For more information contact Derrick or Crystal Kinney at 310-2590</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="76" date="20030915" expires="20031022" showOnHomepage="false">
			<title>Radio Ministry Note</title>
			<detail>Pastor Allen's 7:30 PM Mon-Fri broadcast on KIXL has moved to 9:30 AM on KBBW 1010AM.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="77" date="20030915" expires="20031020" showOnHomepage="false">
			<title>Women's Ministry Worship Team</title>
			<detail>The Women's Ministry is in need of a Women's Worship Team, both vocalist and instrumentalist. Contact Heather Reynolds (565-3859) if you are interested in becoming a part of the team.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="78" date="20030915" expires="20031030" showOnHomepage="false">
			<title>Women Helping Women</title>
			<detail>This ministry offers prayer, spiritual guidance, and support to any woman who makes Calvary Chapel her church home. For an appointment, call the church office during normal working hours.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="79" date="20030915" expires="20031030" showOnHomepage="false">
			<title>Men's Bible Study</title>
			<detail>Sign up today at the Events Center for a study involving the New Testament Men of Faith. This class will meet every other Tuesday evening at 7PM starting on Sept 23.</detail>
		</news-item>
<news-item id="80" date="20031004" expires="20031115" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Operation Christmas Child</title>
			<detail>Fill an empty shoebox with children's toys and necessities and transform it into a child's treasure chest. Brochures are available at the Events Center. Treasure chests are due on or before Nov 23.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="81" date="20031004" expires="20031130" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>The Cupboard</title>
			<detail>Our food pantry will provide food to families in the body of Calvary during times of need. You may donate non-perishable food and personal hygiene items. Place donations in the Collection Area near the restrooms. If you need assistance from this ministry, contact the church office. For more information contact Derrick or Crystal Kinney at 310-2590</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="82" date="20031004" expires="20031016" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Extended Worship Service</title>
			<detail>Join us for a time of extended worship of the Lord during our regular 7pm Wednesday service Oct 15.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="83" date="20031004" expires="20031031" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Preorder Your "LIVE" Worship CD!</title>
			<detail>You may support our recording project by preordering the Calvary Austin Worship CD at a 20% discount for $12. Come by the Events Center today. This offer is good only through this week.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="83" date="20031024" expires="20031116" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Multimedia Volunteers Needed</title>
			<detail>The Media Ministry is in need of volunteers to help in the Video and Streaming Media areas. No experience is necessary, we will provide the training. All you need is a servant's heart. <link href="jeremy@calvaryaustin.org">Contact Jeremy</link> if you are interested in becoming a part of the team.</detail>
		</news-item>
	</news>
</content>
