<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- 

	What's New
	
	$Id: whatsnew.xml,v 1.94 2004/07/16 20:44:42 tie Exp $
		
-->
<content title="What's New" base=".">
	<news>
		<news-item id="29" date="20030430" expires="20030430" showOnHomepage="true">
			<logo align="right" img="../images/YEV02a.jpg" alt="Year End Video"/>
			<title>2002 Year End Video</title>
			<detail>Check out the <link href="http://www.calvarychapel.org/austin/video/2002yeva.ram">Year End Video</link> with your <link href="http://www.real.com">RealVideo</link> player!</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="30" date="20030430" expires="20030430" showOnHomepage="true">
			<logo align="right" img="../images/YEV02b.jpg" alt="Year In Review Video"/>
			<title>2002 Year In Review Video</title>
			<detail>Check out the <link href="http://www.calvarychapel.org/austin/video/2002yevb.ram">Year In Review Video</link> with your <link href="http://www.real.com">RealVideo</link> player!</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="31" date="20030401" expires="20030401" showOnHomepage="false">
			<title>Marriage Ministry</title>
			<detail>The Spring group meetings begin this week. If you signed up, your books will be available at the first meeting. <link href="../ministries/marriage.html">Learn more...</link>
			</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="32" date="20030201" expires="20030315" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Children's Ministry</title>
			<detail>Several volunteer positions are open on Sunday and Wednesday.  Please check the Calvary Kids Hallway board for more info. It is very important to pick up, at various places in the lobby, a schedule of training sessions if you've signed up.  There are sessions Apr 6, during the 2nd or 3rd services and also on Apr 13.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="33" date="20030301" expires="20030319" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Stop and Seek</title>
			<detail>Please join us this Wednesday evening, Mar 19, at 7PM, as Pastor Allen leads us in the last of four special services devoted to prayer and waiting for a word from the Lord for each of us, our families and our church.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="34" date="20030301" expires="20030319" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Calvary Bookstore </title>
			<detail>Several volunteer positions are open on Sundays and Wednesdays.  Please contact Andrea Rigg at the church office (719.4667) or come by the bookstore for more information.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="35" date="20030301" expires="20030401" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Children's Ministry Sign In</title>
			<detail>The new sign in system will begin April 6.  Pick up a flyer and a form to be filled out in the Children's Ministry area today.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="36" date="20030301" expires="20030327" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Men's Ministry</title>
			<detail>Starting Tuesday the men’s bible study will meet every Tuesday night until the end of May.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="37" date="20030320" expires="20030418" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>New Home Fellowship</title>
			<detail>A new home group will start meeting on Friday, Apr 11, at 7:30PM in Cedar Park.  It will be lead by James Lozano and hosted by James and Talinda Higginbotham (1800 Nelson Ranch Loop).  Flyers with directions are available in the lobby.  Contact the Higginbotham's (336.8493) for more information.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="38" date="20030320" expires="20030418" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Young Disciples Club</title>
			<detail>“YDC” is a discipleship club for Wise Guys, Witnesses and Watchmen--boys and girls K-5th grade.  There is worship, Bible, game and group times each Wednesday evening.  Pick up a YDC flyer at the Octopus in the lobby for more information.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="39" date="20030406" expires="20030406" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Daylight Saving Time</title>
			<detail>Next Sunday, April 6, is the time to “spring forward” by setting clocks ahead 1 hour Saturday night.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="40" date="20030403" expires="20030406" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Leander Home Fellowship</title>
			<detail>The Leander Home Fellowship has a new meeting location.  For more information, call Robert and Sandra Verastegui (259.0251).</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="41" date="20030301" expires="20030501" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>God Bless Our Military Serving in Iraq</title>
			<detail>We want to pray for all those who are serving and their families.  We want to pray especially for our own Calvary families.  If you are a member of one of those families or know of one, please call the office (719-4667) so we may pray for them by name!</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="42" date="20030404" expires="20030501" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Bookstore</title>
			<detail>Want to grow deeper in your walk with the Lord?  There's something for everyone in the family including great music, journals, and books for kids.  If you can't find what you're looking for, we can order it for you.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="43" date="20030302" expires="20030601" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Release Your Inner Geek</title>
			<detail>The gospel presented in multimedia - from streaming video/audio to web servers, networking, and programming. Join the Internet Ministry as we take God's Word to the world and serve the body of Calvary Austin! Join in the fun and serve the Lord with your skills. <link href="mailto:webservant-austin@calvarychapel.org">Contact the web ministry</link> or visit the <link href="../ministries/internet.html">Internet Ministry Page</link> to learn how you can be a part of this exciting outreach.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="44" date="20030402" expires="20030601" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Women's Ministry</title>
			<detail>Our Women¹s Ministry is offering 2 studies, Jun 3 through Aug 12. A bible study titled "Healed and Set Free" will meet every Tuesday, 7-9PM. Sharing will be in very small groups.  And a study titled "Principles for Women in Leadership", designed for those desiring to know more about women¹s leadership will meet every other Tuesday, 7-9PM. Sign up at the Events Center.
</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="45" date="20030418" expires="20030425" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Women's Retreat Tapes</title>
			<detail>Audio tapes from the women’s retreat are now available.  Place your order at the Media Center in the lobby.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="46" date="20030511" expires="20030530" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Frontline Worship CD</title>
			<detail>Gracemongers, one of the FrontLine Worship teams has released their CD.  It is available in the bookstore for $10.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="47" date="20030511" expires="20030602" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Free Indeed Addictions Ministry</title>
			<detail>Calvary Austin is introducing a new internet-based ministry to address pornography, substance abuse, overeating, smoking or other addictions.  If you need help in one of these areas or would like to serve in this ministry visit the <link href="../ministries/freeindeed.html">ministry's home page</link></detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="48" date="20030511" expires="20030602" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>The Cupboard</title>
			<detail>Our food pantry provides food to families in the body of Calvary during times of need.  If you need assistance from this ministry, contact the church office.
</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="49" date="20030518" expires="20030713" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Children's Conference Hosting</title>
			<detail>Would you like to bless one or more peope attending our CM Conference from out of town with accommodations in your home?  If interested, sign up to be a host family at the Events Center.
</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="50" date="20030522" expires="20030714" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Crown Financial Ministry</title>
			<detail>There are still some spaces left for the course on handling money God's way.  Sign up at the Events Center today.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="51" date="20030522" expires="20030712" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Bookstore</title>
			<detail>Want to grow deeper in your walk with the Lord?  Stop and check-out all the Bibles, books, study guides and CDs.  Open after every Wednesday and Sunday service.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="52" date="20030529" expires="20030720" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Fan Drive</title>
			<detail>Calvary Singles is sponsoring the 3rd annual fan drive for Eldercare.  Purchase a fan and drop it off in our new Collection Area in the hall near the restroom.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<!--
		<news-item id="53" date="20030529" expires="20030616" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Calvary T-Shirt Blowout Sale</title>
			<detail>Want to wear a Calvary t-shirt to the Baptism/Picnic?  Visit the bookstore and purchase one for only $3.00. Choose from many children¹s sizes.  A few adult sizes remain.</detail>
		</news-item>
		-->
		<news-item id="54" date="20030703" expires="20030729" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Seasoned Saints Fellowship</title>
			<detail>A new ministry has started.  Seasoned Saints is for those special folks in our church who, by the grace of God, have been a part of this world for a good spell longer than most others and have so much to offer by their presence.  We'll meet at the church the 1st Sunday of each month starting July 6, at 5PM for fellowship.  Pick up a flyer at the Info Center or call for more information</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="55" date="20030704" expires="20030712" showOnHomepage="false">
			<title>Lunch with Calvary Continuum</title>
			<detail>Calvary Continuum, on 590AM KIXL, has moved to 12:00pm and 7:30pm every weekday. Spend your lunch break listening to Allen's message</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="56" date="20030712" expires="20030828" showOnHomepage="false">
			<title>Worshippers Wanted!!</title>
			<detail>Participate in the "live" recording of our first worship CD. The recording will take place over two evenings, Aug 26 and 27 beginning at 7PM. Come sing and be a part of this worship experience. Childcare will be provided on Tues for ages 2 years through 5th grade.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="57" date="20030712" expires="20030927" showOnHomepage="false">
			<title>Men's Retreat</title>
			<detail>Registration continues until Aug 31th for the Sept 25-27 retreat at T-Bar-M Ranch in New Braunfels. The main speaker is Ken Graves from Calvary Chapel Bangor, Maine. Sign up at the Events Center.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="58" date="20030712" expires="20030930" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Prayer Chain</title>
			<detail>Members of the body of Calvary are encouraged to contact the Prayer Chain with prayer needs so those who are a part of the ministry may lift them up to the Lord (479-9454).</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="59" date="20030712" expires="20030720" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>The Cupboard</title>
			<detail>Our food pantry will provide food to families in the body of Calvary during times of need. You may donate non-perishable food and personal hygiene items. Place donations in the Collection Area near the restrooms. If you need assistance from this ministry, contact the church office. For more information contact Derrick or Crystal Kinney (310-2590).</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="60" date="20030712" expires="20030720" showOnHomepage="false">
			<title>Bookstore</title>
			<detail>Check-out all the Bibles, books, study guides, journals, and books for kids. You can also special order. The bookstore is open after every Wednesday and Sunday service.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="61" date="20030712" expires="20030720" showOnHomepage="false">
			<title>Audio</title>
			<detail>Pastor Allen's messages are available on tape, CD, and MP3 after every service in the lobby. Tape catalogs are also available.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="62" date="20030712" expires="20030720" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Radio, TV and Internet</title>
			<detail>Hear Pastor Allen on Calvary Continuum at NOON and 7:30PM on KIXL 970AM or watch our television program on cable access channel 11 Saturdays at NOON. Watch select services live on the internet or check out the audio archive on our web site.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="63" date="20030809" expires="20030831" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>School of Ministry</title>
			<detail>Interested in learning more about apologetics, theology, church history, small group ministry, evangelism or inductive Bible study? We are taking signups until Aug 31th at the Events Center. School of Ministry begins Sept 8th and meets on Wednesdays at 7PM at the church.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="64" date="20030809" expires="20030829" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Scholarships Needed</title>
			<detail>If you would like to give a partial or full scholarship for a poor college student to attend the 2003 Mid-South College and Career Retreat on Labor Day weekend, go by the Events Center.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="65" date="20030810" expires="20030816" showOnHomepage="false">
			<title>Bookstore</title>
			<detail>Check-out all the Bibles, books, study guides, journals, and books for kids. You can also special order. The bookstore is open after every Wednesday and Sunday service.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="66" date="20030810" expires="20030816" showOnHomepage="false">
			<title>Audio</title>
			<detail>Pastor Allen's messages are available on tape, CD, and MP3 after every service in the lobby. Tape catalogs are also available.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="67" date="20030810" expires="20030812" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Radio, TV and Internet</title>
			<detail>Hear Pastor Allen on Calvary Continuum at NOON and 7:30PM on KIXL 970AM or watch our television program on cable access channel 11 Saturdays at NOON. Watch select services live on the internet or check out the audio archive on our web site.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="68" date="20030824" expires="20030912" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Preorder Your "Live" Worship CD!</title>
			<detail>You may support our recording project by preordering the Calvary Austin Worship CD at a 20% discount for $12. Come by the Events Center today.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="69" date="20030824" expires="20030912" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>New Believers' Class</title>
			<detail>The 12-week class in basic Bible fundamentals meets on Mondays at 7PM in the New Parents room starting Sept 8th. Sign up at the Events Center.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="70" date="20030824" expires="20030923" showOnHomepage="false">
			<title>Women's Fall Bible Studies</title>
			<detail>Sign up at the Events Center for the "Face-to-Face with Women of the Bible" study. The costs is $13. The Tuesday Morning Study will begin Sept 23rd, meet at 10AM, and provide cooperative childcare. The Tuesday Evening Study will begin Sept 16th, meet every other Tuesday at 7PM, and will not provide childcare.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="71" date="20030825" expires="20030925" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Radio, TV and Internet</title>
			<detail>Hear Pastor Allen on Calvary Continuum at NOON on KIXL 970AM or at 9:30AM on 1010AM. Watch our television program on cable access channel 11 Saturdays at NOON. Watch select services live on the internet or check out the audio archive on our web site.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="72" date="20030825" expires="20030916" showOnHomepage="false">
			<title>Audio</title>
			<detail>Pastor Allen's messages are available on tape, CD, and MP3 after every service in the lobby. Tape catalogs are also available.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="73" date="20030825" expires="20030930" showOnHomepage="false">
			<title>Bookstore</title>
			<detail>Check-out our large selection of books. You can also special order. The bookstore is open after every Wednesday and Sunday service.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="74" date="20030905" expires="20030923" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Toddler Teacher Needed</title>
			<detail>The Women's Tuesday Morning Bible Study is in need of a paid teacher to teach the toddlers(ages 10 - 35 months) while their moms attend the study. The hours are from 9:40 AM to 11:40 AM starting Sept 23rd. If yor are interested in the position, please contact Vicky Lozano at 336-8368.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="75" date="20030905" expires="20031010" showOnHomepage="false">
			<title>The Cupboard</title>
			<detail>Our food pantry will provide food to families in the body of Calvary during times of need. You may donate non-perishable food and personal hygiene items. Place donations in the Collection Area near the restrooms. If you need assistance from this ministry, contact the church office. For more information contact Derrick or Crystal Kinney at 310-2590</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="76" date="20030915" expires="20031022" showOnHomepage="false">
			<title>Radio Ministry Note</title>
			<detail>Pastor Allen's 7:30 PM Mon-Fri broadcast on KIXL has moved to 9:30 AM on KBBW 1010AM.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="77" date="20030915" expires="20031020" showOnHomepage="false">
			<title>Women's Ministry Worship Team</title>
			<detail>The Women's Ministry is in need of a Women's Worship Team, both vocalist and instrumentalist. Contact Heather Reynolds (565-3859) if you are interested in becoming a part of the team.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="78" date="20030915" expires="20031030" showOnHomepage="false">
			<title>Women Helping Women</title>
			<detail>This ministry offers prayer, spiritual guidance, and support to any woman who makes Calvary Chapel her church home. For an appointment, call the church office during normal working hours.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="79" date="20030915" expires="20031030" showOnHomepage="false">
			<title>Men's Bible Study</title>
			<detail>Sign up today at the Events Center for a study involving the New Testament Men of Faith. This class will meet every other Tuesday evening at 7PM starting on Sept 23.</detail>
		</news-item>
<news-item id="80" date="20031004" expires="20031115" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Operation Christmas Child</title>
			<detail>Fill an empty shoebox with children's toys and necessities and transform it into a child's treasure chest. Brochures are available at the Events Center. Treasure chests are due on or before Nov 23.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="81" date="20031004" expires="20031130" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>The Cupboard</title>
			<detail>Our food pantry will provide food to families in the body of Calvary during times of need. You may donate non-perishable food and personal hygiene items. Place donations in the Collection Area near the restrooms. If you need assistance from this ministry, contact the church office. For more information contact Derrick or Crystal Kinney at 310-2590</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="82" date="20031004" expires="20031016" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Extended Worship Service</title>
			<detail>Join us for a time of extended worship of the Lord during our regular 7pm Wednesday service Oct 15.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="83" date="20031004" expires="20031031" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Preorder Your "LIVE" Worship CD!</title>
			<detail>You may support our recording project by preordering the Calvary Austin Worship CD at a 20% discount for $12. Come by the Events Center today. This offer is good only through this week.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="83" date="20031024" expires="20031206" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Multimedia Volunteers Needed</title>
			<detail>The Media Ministry is in need of volunteers to help in the Video and Streaming Media areas. No experience is necessary, we will provide the training. All you need is a servant's heart. <link href="jeremy@calvaryaustin.org">Contact Jeremy</link> if you are interested in becoming a member of the team.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="84" date="20031101" expires="20031106" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Pastors and Leaders Conference</title>
			<detail>The Mid-South and Leaders Conference is this week. Two of the sessions are open to those not signed up. Come Thursday and Friday evenings, Nov 6-7, at 7:00 pm.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="85" date="20031114" expires="20031205" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Christmas Adoptions</title>
			<detail>The Children's Ministry is once again adopting children from our local neighborhood elementary schools to help out with meals and gifts during this Christmas season. All collections due Dec 7th. Sign up this week at the Events Center. For more information call Donna Cano(255.7756)</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="86" date="20031116" expires="20031123" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Actresses Needed</title>
			<detail>Two female roles are available in a short drama to be part of Calvary's Christmas Eve service. One character is in her late teens, and the other is in her late 30's-early 40's. Roles must be cast before Thanksgiving with final auditions on Nov 23rd. Contact Nikki Zook(656.2631) ASAP to schedule an audition or for more information.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="87" date="20031116" expires="20031130" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Crown Financial Ministry</title>
			<detail>Do you have a budget? Do you live within it? Do you have a current will, savings/investment plan, debt repayment plan, giving plan, and do they align with God's Word? Come learn what the Bible teaches about these things, make some new friends, and learn how to develop and manage these practical tools relating to finances. Stop by the Events Center today for details. Sign up and payment deadline is Sunday Nov 29th.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="88" date="20031116" expires="20031228" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Marriage Ministry</title>
			<detail>Beginning in January, come join the many couples going through the Home Builder's curriculum. Topics include overcoming stress, building your mate's self-esteem, raising children of faith, making remarriage last, and mastering money. Cost for books are $8-$10. Groups meet weekly for 6 to 7 weeks. Space is limited. Sign up today at the Events Center. Registration deadline is Dec 28th.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="89" date="20031116" expires="20031130" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Win and Equip Our Children</title>
			<detail>Be a part of the Young Disciples Club (YDC). To maintain a quality discipleship club, we need several volunteers. We have a flexible monthly schedule. A YDC table will be in the Children's Ministry Hall after each service or contact Dee Dee Michell(512.759.2040).</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="90" date="20031204" expires="20031231" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>"LIVE" Worship CD!</title>
			<detail>The LIVE Worship CD now has an expected release date of Jan 2004. Sorry for any inconvenience; it will be worth the wait!</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="91" date="20031207" expires="20040307" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>School of Ministry</title>
			<detail>We are taking sign-ups at the Events Center for the semester of classes to begin March 8.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="92" date="20031207" expires="20031231" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Usher Ministry</title>
			<detail>Wanted: Men who want to serve in this ministry. Call Johnny Arnold at 719.9060</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="93" date="20031219" expires="20031231" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Calvary Discipleship Program</title>
			<detail>Now taking sign-ups for 101, 201 and
301 classes. More information at the Events Center.</detail>
		</news-item>
	<news-item id="94" date="20031219" expires="20040110" showOnHomepage="false">
			<title>Home Fellowship</title>
			<detail>Effective Jan. 9 the home fellowship group currently meeting at the Uk residence will begin meeting at 1405 Willow Bluff Drive, Pflugerville at the Schumacher's. Contact number 252.7612. Group leaders: Matt Lang and Ken Henderson. Flyers with map and contact information are in the lobby.</detail>
	</news-item>
	<news-item id="95" date="20040103" expires="20040201" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Schedule Changes: 3-2-1</title>
			<detail>What does 3-2-1 stand for? We are moving from 3 services to 2 services on Feb 1 (2-1). We will also take the opportunity to introduce a slight time adjustment to allow for better traffic flow in the parking lot and children's ministry areas. Effective Sunday Feb 1, we will have two morning services; times are 9:30 AM and 11:30 AM.</detail>
	</news-item>
	<news-item id="96" date="20040109" expires="20040131" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Super Duper Bowl</title>
			<detail>Why go to Houston when you can play football right here. Come join us Saturday Jan 31 from 9-11am. Flyer with more information at the Events Center.</detail>
	</news-item>
		<news-item id="97" date="20040117" expires="20040326" showOnHomepage="false">
			<title>Women's Retreat</title>
			<detail>Registration for the 2004 Women's Retreat at Camp Balcones Springs begins January 25. Register early and receive a discount! Come by the Events Center for more information and to register.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="98" date="20040117" expires="20041011" showOnHomepage="false">
			<title>Israel Trip</title>
			<detail>The long anticipated tour of Israel is scheduled for October 11 - 21, 2004. Flyers now available at the Events Center. For more information contact Bunjee Garrett at Bunjee@calvaryaustin.org or 719-4467.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="99" date="20040117" expires="20040201" showOnHomepage="false">
			<title>Volunteers Needed</title>
			<detail>Share your clerical skills and meet new people! The church office needs friendly people to help answer the phones from 1:00PM to 5:00PM, Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday, or Friday. Call the office for more information.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="100" date="20040124" expires="20040208" showOnHomepage="false">
			<title>Volunteer Opportunity</title>
			<detail>Do you have a desire to see Christ and Calvary Chapel through coffee? Coffee Creator wants you. For more information, see Brooke Johnson at Coffee Creator or call her at 719-4544 or by email at coffeecreator@calvaryaustin.org </detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="101" date="20040124" expires="20040208" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>The Cupboard</title>
			<detail>Please do not bring candy, soda pop, cookware, clothing, or other similar items for the food pantry. We can only stock non-perishable food items in our limited space. Thank you for your faithfulness and generosity.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="102" date="20040124" expires="20040212" showOnHomepage="false">
			<title>Radio, TV and Internet</title>
			<detail>Hear Pastor Allen on Calvary Continuum at NOON and 7:30PM on KIXL 970AM or watch our television program on cable access channel 11 Saturdays at NOON. Watch select services live on the internet or check out the audio archive on our web site.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="103" date="20040117" expires="20040211" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Bring Out Your Inner Geek</title>
			<detail>The Internet Ministry is looking for people who have a willingness to minister to one another and serve the body with the following skills: IT, networking, Linux server management, HTML, web designers/graphics artists, and Java developers. Contact internet@calvaryaustin.org for more information.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="104" date="20040124" expires="20040328" showOnHomepage="false">
			<title>Volunteers Needed</title>
			<detail>The Tape/CD Ministry is looking for volunteers with a servant's heart to help sell tapes. Visit the Tape Booth for more information.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="105" date="20040124" expires="20040228" showOnHomepage="false">
			<title>Intercessory Prayer Group </title>
			<detail>New Christians, mature Christians, anyone with a heart for prayer is invited to join the Intercessory Prayer Connection for intercessory prayer. Please meet us in the prayer room during the 9:30 AM Sunday service.</detail>
		</news-item>
			<news-item id="106" date="20040105" expires="20040427" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Calvary Austin Music WebPage</title>
			<detail>The new <link href="http://www.calvaryaustinmusic.org">Calvary Austin Music WebPage</link> is here! Check out the new CD release <strong>"I Will"</strong>, learn the stories behind the songs, and much more!</detail>
   </news-item>
		<news-item id="107" date="20040321" expires="20040428" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Bookstore</title>
			<detail>Check-out all the Bibles, books, study guides, journals, and books for kids. You can also special order. The bookstore is open after every Wednesday and Sunday service.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="108" date="20040201" expires="20040228" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Missing Your Bible?</title>
			<detail>Please check the bible lost and found table in the lobby if you have misplaced your bible. We will donate all unclaimed bibles to other ministries.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="109" date="20040206" expires="20040227" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Greeting Ministry</title>
			<detail>Looking for a place to get plugged in at Calvary? We need friendly men and women to share God's love as people walk through the doors. Opportunities are available for both services on Sunday, and Wednesday. For more information, call Matt Lang at 512-989-8575 or send an email to Langm@fms-regional.com</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="110" date="20040206" expires="20040327" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Calling All Bookworms</title>
			<detail>Come make new friends while serving the body of Christ selling books! Call Andrea at 719-4667, or drop by the bookstore.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="111" date="20040206" expires="20040221" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Thursday Playdate</title>
			<detail>Come laugh and play with other Moms every Thursday morning at 10:00 am. Kids are welcome too! For location and information, call Angela Laughlin at 238-7333.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="112" date="20040215" expires="20040329" showOnHomepage="false">
			<title>Worship CD</title>
			<detail>The Calvary Austin Worship CD is expected to arrive before Feb 29. We will continue to pre-sale the CD for $12 at the Events Center until CD's are received, at which time they will be available for $15 in the Bookstore.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="113" date="20040215" expires="20040229" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Urgent Volunteer Need</title>
			<detail>Do you have a desire to serve Christ and Calvary Chapel through coffee? For more information see Brooke Johnson at Coffee Creator, call her at 719-4544, or by email at coffeecreator@calvaryaustin.org.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="114" date="20040227" expires="20040423" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>Bring Out Your Inner Geek</title>
			<detail>The Internet Ministry is seeking people who
have a willingness to minister to one another and serve the body with
the following skills: IT, networking, Linux server management, HTML,
web designers/graphic artists, and Java developers. If you are
interested in joining this exciting ministry, please contact
internet@calvaryaustin.org.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="115" date="20040227" expires="20040427" showOnHomepage="true">
			<title>"Free Indeed" Addictions Ministry</title>
			<detail>Calvary Austin is introducing a new internet-based ministry to address pornography, substance abuse, overeating, smoking or other addictions. If you need help in one of these areas or would like to serve in this ministry see the new web page under the Ministries link from the Calvary Homepage.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="116" date="20040227" expires="20040427" showOnHomepage="false">
			<title>Audio</title>
			<detail>Pastor Allen's messages are available on tape, CD, and MP3 after every service in the lobby. Tape catalogs are also available.</detail></news-item>
			<news-item id="117" date="20040327" expires="20040427" showOnHomepage="false">
			<title>Radio, TV &amp; Internet</title>
			<detail>Hear Pastor Allen on Calvary Continuum NOON on
970AM or at 9:30am on 1010AM. Watch our tv program on cable access
channel 11 Saturdays at NOON.  Watch select services live on the
internet or check out the audio archive on our web site.</detail></news-item>
	<news-item id="118" date="20040101" expires="20040411" showOnHomepage="true">
		<title>www.easterservice.com</title>
		<detail>We are creatively publicizing our Easter Service at local theaters between movies. Help us get the word out and check out the site. There are pre-printed Good Friday/Easter Service invitation cards in the lobby to use to <strong>invite</strong> those you are <strong>investing</strong> in.</detail>
	</news-item>
	<news-item id="119" date="20040401" expires="20040503" showOnHomepage="true">
		<title>CDP</title>
		<detail>Calvary Discipleship Program classes will begin again on Monday nights starting May 3rd through June 7th. Sign up now at the Events Center for the 101, 201, 301 class.</detail>
	</news-item>
	<news-item id="120" date="20040401" expires="20040423" showOnHomepage="true">
		<title>VBS Fair and Registration</title>
		<detail>On April 18 look for the Olympic flag and stop by to get a sneak preview of this year's Vacation Bible School. Children who register at the fair will receive a small gift; parents who stop by will have a chance to see how they can help make this year's VBS success. For more information contact Kerry Schroeder at 219-7028.</detail>
	</news-item>
	<news-item id="121" date="20040401" expires="20040516" showOnHomepage="true">
		<title>The Cupboard</title>
		<detail> Our food pantry will provide food to families within Calvary during times of need. You may donate non-perishable food and personal hygiene items. Place donations in the Collection Area near the restrooms. If you need assistance from this ministry, contact the church office.</detail>
	</news-item>
	<news-item id="122" date="20040401" expires="20040516" showOnHomepage="true">
		<title>Volunteers for Events Center</title>
		<detail>If you are interested, outgoing, personal, and like to meet people, come to the Events Center to fill out a ministry application.</detail>
	</news-item>
	<news-item id="123" date="20040401" expires="20040630" showOnHomepage="false">
		<title>Sip on This</title>
		<detail>Coffee Creator is in need of volunteers to serve in various capacities. To satisfy further cravings contact Debbie at 719-4544 or stop by Coffee Creator.</detail>
	</news-item>
	<news-item id="124" date="20040401" expires="20040423" showOnHomepage="false">
		<title>Building Momentum</title>
		<detail>If you missed Kick-off Sunday, please stop on your way out of the auditorium and request a brochure from our ushers.</detail>
	</news-item>
	<news-item id="125" date="20040428" expires="20040630" showOnHomepage="false">
		<title>Enjoy Cooking?</title>
		<detail>If so, then Fishes and Loaves need you! This ministry seeks to serve the body of Calvary Chapel by providing prepared meals during times of special need. Visit the Events Center for more details of contact Brian or Stacy Scott at stacy@austin.rr.com or 512-252-0021.</detail>
	</news-item>
	<news-item id="126" date="20040428" expires="20040626" showOnHomepage="true">
		<title>Web Designers Wanted!</title>
		<detail>If you are interested in joining the Calvary Austin Web Team on any level, please contact Bunjee Garrett at the church. 512-719-4667.</detail>
	</news-item>
	<news-item id="127" date="20040428" expires="20040527" showOnHomepage="true">
		<title>Motley Crew Needed</title>
		<detail>Not musically, but facility speaking. The "Facility Team" is expanding to meet various needs within our current location.You can come and learn more about this great opportunity by joining us by a breakfast on Saturday May 1st at 8am in the Youth Room. Contact Glendon Nicks at 512-719-4667 for more information.</detail>
	</news-item>
	<news-item id="128" date="20040428" expires="20040526" showOnHomepage="true">
		<title>Free Building Momentum CD</title>
		<detail>Pick up an "Audio Study Guide: What the Bible Says About Giving" at the Building Momentum Info Wall in the lobby, or access the guide by going to <link href="http://www.calvaryaustin.org/buildingmomentum">www.calvaryaustin.org/buildingmomentum</link> online.</detail>
	</news-item>
	   <!--news-item id="129" date="20040530" expires="20041015" showOnHomepage="false">
		<title>Men's Retreat 2004</title>
		<detail>Join us at Camp Tejas on Oct. 15-16 for the 2004 Men's Retreat. Pastor Art Murillo of The Way Christian Church in Chula Vista, California, will be hosting this event. You can find information in the church lobby or at the Men's Ministry web page <link href="http://www.calvaryaustin.org/ministries/men.html">www.calvaryaustin.org/ministries/men.html</link> online.</detail>
		</news-item-->
	   <news-item id="130" date="20040604" expires="20040718" showOnHomepage="true">
		   <title>Fan Drive</title>
		   <detail>Don't forget to bring your fans for the 4th annual fan drive benefiting the elderly. Calvary Singles will collect the fans until July 17th.</detail>
		</news-item>
	   <news-item id="131" date="20040604" expires="20040718" showOnHomepage="true">
		   <title>Submit Your God Stories</title>
		   <detail>Tell us what miracles and mighty works God has done in your life. Please send your stories and pictures to : <link href="mailto:godstories@kaply.com">godstories@kaply.com</link> or drop them off at the Events Center for Cynde Kaply.</detail>
		</news-item>
	   <news-item id="132" date="20040504" expires="20040718" showOnHomepage="true">
		   <title>"Calvary Responder"</title>
		   <detail>We are forming an emergency response team. If you are experienced with emergency procedures and interested, please sign up at the Events Center.</detail>
		</news-item>
	   <news-item id="133" date="20040504" expires="20040718" showOnHomepage="false">
		   <title>Vital Life Jr. High</title>
		   <detail>Starting Sunday, June 6th, there will only be one Jr. High Sunday service. It will be offered during the 2nd service. If you have any questions or concerns, contact David Robinson or email: <link href="mailto:vitallifecrew@yahoo.com">vitallifecrew@yahoo.com</link>vitallifecrew@yahoo.com</detail>
		</news-item>
	   <news-item id="134" date="20040604" expires="20040718" showOnHomepage="false">
		   <title>Israel Trip</title>
		   <detail>If you are signed up for the Israel Trip, there is an information packet waiting for you at the Events Center.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="135" date="20040604" expires="20040903" showOnHomepage="true">
		   <title>College and Career Retreat</title>
		   <detail>Join us for the College and Career 2004 Retreat. The retreat will be Sep. 3-5 at <link href="http://www.texasretreat.com">Balcones Retreat Center</link>. The cost is $130. To make a downpayment or to register, stop by the Events Center.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="136" date="20040622" expires="20070622" showOnHomepage="true">
		   <title>Buildling Momentum Informational Web Site</title>
		   <detail>Please visit the Calvary Austin <link href="http://www.calvaryaustin.org/buildingmomentum/index.html">Building Momentum Web Site</link>. Check the web site for the latest information about the Calvary Austin building project.</detail>
		</news-item>
		<news-item id="137" date="20040622" expires="20050622" showOnHomepage="true">
		   <title>Calvary Austin Music Web Site</title>
		   <detail>Please visit the <link href="http://www.calvaryaustinmusic.org">Calvary Austin Music</link> web site . You can get the latest information about the newest worhsip team CD release, "I Will", as well as information about TV and radio appearances. Go check it out!</detail>
		</news-item>
	   <news-item id="138" date="20040622" expires="20040731" showOnHomepage="true">
		   <title>Sip on This</title>
		   <detail>Coffee Creator is in need of volunteers to serve in various capacities. To satisfy further cravings contact Debbie at 719-4554 or stop by Coffee Creator.</detail>
		</news-item>
	   <news-item id="139" date="20040622" expires="20040731" showOnHomepage="true">
		   <title>Administrative Ministry Volunteers Sought </title>
		   <detail>If you have a heart to serve the Lord, the staff, and the church body, please call Katherine at 719-4667.</detail>
		</news-item>
<!--
-->
  </news>
</content>
