<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
	Bunjee Garrett Bio - Part of the Staff Bios

	$Id: bunjee.xml,v 1.3 2004/08/23 21:20:39 premav Exp $

-->

<content title="Brief Bio of Bunjee Garrett">
<heading>Meet Bunjee Garrett</heading>
<br></br>
<img src="../images/staff/bunjeeweb.jpg" alt="Bunjee Garrett"/>
<heading>Spouse</heading>
<p>Brenda</p>

<heading>Children</heading>
<p>None</p>

<heading>Very Brief Testimony</heading>
<p>I aspired to be a famous artist and musician and spent several years building a career and living the life that comes along with the underground art and music community. The closer I came to success, the emptier I felt which brought me to the conclusion that success would not bring the happiness that I thought it would bring. I began to look into various world-views like the new age movement and Asian meditation practices which I knew very quickly could not change the emptiness I felt inside. I ran into a friend who had obviously found real peace which he credited to Jesus Christ. After a few months of many questions, conversations, debates and soul searching, I asked Jesus to forgive me and renew my heart. He HAS changed my life and continues to make my character more like His. All glory to God alone.</p>

<heading>Favorite Book of the Bible and Why</heading>
<p>I can't decide between Acts, Hebrews and Romans.</p>
<p>Acts is certainly a favorite because I love the play by play feel of Luke's account dealing with the acts of the 1st century church.</p> 
<p>I love Romans too because of the well orchestrated argument that Paul develops revealing the sinful state of every man and the opportunity for every man to be justified freely by the free gift of God's grace which was paid for by our Saviour, Jesus Christ upon the cross.</p> 


I also enjoy Hebrews immensely because of the way Paul uses the principle of analogy to reveal the meanings of the Old Testament customs and rituals. Quite insightful! 

<heading>Favorite Verse and Why</heading>
<p>Rom 5:1* Therefore, having been justified by faith, we have peace with God through our Lord Jesus Christ, 
2* through whom also we have access by faith into this grace in which we stand, and rejoice in hope of the glory of God.</p>
<p>Romans 4 and 5 are two of my favorite chapters in the Bible because I love to study the doctrine of Imputation. Romans 5:1 and 2 reveal the benefits of having received Christ's righteousness, the fact of justification which is the basis for peace with God. </p>

<heading>Favorite Book (besides the Bible) and Why</heading>
<p>"The Soul Winner"</p> 
<p>Author: C. H. Spurgeon</p>
<p>Why: This is the book that set my heart on fire to win the lost to Christ which has been the joy of my life.</p>

<heading>Who do you most admire (besides Jesus)</heading>
<p>There are several people whom I admire for different reasons. First of all, Chuck Smith is most admirable for his humility and sense of Spiritual guidance. I also admire my Pastor, Allen Rigg. He exemplifies discipline and obedience. Norman Giesler is by far one of the great thinkers on the Earth today. His work has had much influence on me. Most of all, I admire Paul the apostle. Paul to me represents a complete package of the three mentioned before. Paul was humble, Spirit led, disciplined and obedient and an extremely gifted thinker. This was all wrapped together in agape love and passed onto us through his epistles. </p>

<heading>What do you do at Calvary</heading>
<p>I oversee and teach for School of Ministry and I oversee the Media Ministry.</p>

<br/>
<br/>
Mail me at <link href="mailto:bunjee@calvaryaustin.org">bunjee@calvaryaustin.org</link>

<br></br>
<br></br>
<br></br>

<p>back to ....<link href="../about/staff.html">Meet Our Staff</link></p>
</content>
