<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
	Donna Cano Bio - Part of the Staff Bios

	$Id: derrick.xml,v 1.5 2004/10/22 15:17:14 premav Exp $

-->

<content title="Brief Bio of Derrick Kinney">
<heading>Meet Derrick Kinney</heading>
<br></br>
<br></br>
<br></br>
<br></br>
<img src="../images/staff/derrickweb.jpg" alt="Derrick Kinney"/>
<heading>Spouse</heading>
<p>Crystal</p>

<heading>Children</heading>
<p>Devon, Darius &amp; D'Mitri</p>

<heading>Very Brief Testimony</heading>
<p>In early 1987 I found myself on a 90-day assignment in Saudi Arabia (Air Force) constantly being bothered by another airman who insisted on engaging in conversations about God, Christ, forgiveness, sin, separation and the whole menu. This guy would share with several guys who would mock and make fun of him. During this time of sharing, I would return to my room and have difficulty sleeping based on the conversations we'd had. On one given night we were assigned on duty together, in a vehicle, all night. Through the course of conversation I was asked, "What's keeping you from inviting Christ into your heart"? I was N A I L E D! I responded, "nothing", and prayed there on the spot for forgiveness and invited Christ into my life, for life.
</p>

<heading>Favorite Book of the Bible and Why</heading>
<p>Toss up between Acts &amp; Ephesians! Acts based the rich history for the early church and Ephesians due Paul giving a very real focus (In Him) and the practical application given for our walk.</p>

<heading>Favorite Verse and Why</heading>
<p>Psalm 37:25 I once was young, but now I'm old: but I never seen the righteous forsaken, nor his seed beg for bread.<br/>This verse for me captures the faithfulness of God in all of our seasons of life. Irrespective of how we see circumstances, God will be a faithful provider.</p>

<heading>Favorite Book (besides the Bible) and Why</heading>
<p>Several of A.W. Tozers works! Reading his works reminds me that God has, was then, and still is marking men &amp; women to speak to the generations!
</p>

<heading>Who do you most admire (besides Jesus)</heading>
<p>Probably my mother! As a single parent she showed great tenacity in raising 8 boys. I have a lot of respect and admiration for those that find themselves in this predicament and overcome.</p>

<heading>What do you do at Calvary</heading>
<p>Pastor of Family Ministries </p>

<br/>
<br/>
Mail me at <link href="mailto:derrick@calvaryaustin.org">derrick@calvaryaustin.org</link>
<br></br>
<br></br>
<br></br>

<p>back to ....<link href="../about/staff.html">Meet Our Staff</link></p>
</content>
