<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
	Donna Cano Bio - Part of the Staff Bios

	$Id: donna.xml,v 1.4 2004/08/24 03:14:51 tie Exp $

-->

<content title="Brief Bio of Donna Cano">
<heading>Future Site of Bio of Donna Cano</heading>
<br></br>
<br></br>
<br></br>
<br></br>
<img src="../images/staff/donnaweb.jpg" alt="Donna Cano"/>
<heading>Spouse</heading>
<p>Rey</p>

<heading>Children</heading>
<p>Jessica, Benjamin, Joseph</p>

<heading>Very Brief Testimony</heading>
<p>At age 17, I realized my emptiness in life and was told only Jesus Christ could fill this void.  I gave my whole heart to Christ and desired immediately to prepare for the mission field, possibly a mexican orphanage.  The Lord has opened many doors for 
mission work right in my own backyard, if you will.  I love each opportunity to deliver the Great news of Christ to others,especially very young others...kids.  They will hopefully get a good start in life as they commit their ways to the Lord at an early age.  This
is my mission field.</p>

<heading>Favorite Book of the Bible and Why</heading>
<p>Romans, because I am constantly reminded of God's incredible plan of reaching down to mankind with His infinite love and mercy.  I desire that my response to an awesome God would be to serve Him tirelessly.</p>

<heading>Favorite Verse and Why</heading>
<p>Phil. 1:21-  "For me to live is Christ andto die isgain".  There is nothing in life worth living for more than God's precious Son, Jesus!  Living and dying to self daily brings completeness to everyday life.</p>

<heading>Favorite Book (besides the Bible) and Why</heading>
<p>Changes often.  I like "On Being a Servant of God".  It is an easy read, yet so impacting and to the point on Christian service.  I also love "Awesome Volunteer" because this is a "rubber meets the road" type book for all who serve children in the setting I do.  
Packed full of wisdom and ideas.</p>

<heading>Who do you most admire (besides Jesus)</heading>
<p>Rey, my husband, for his great support in all we do together in ministry, even though he has another full-time job.  His patience and protective heart amazes me.  I also love Old Testament, Joseph, because he had big dreams, and through the toughest of 
circumstances he recognizes the sovereignty of His Maker, and never loses hope or spoils the chance to trust and obey and leave the results to God.  Whew!</p>

<heading>What do you do at Calvary</heading>
<p>The Lord blessed me with oversight of our Children's Ministry.</p>

<br/>
<br/>
Mail me at <link href="mailto:donna@calvaryaustin.org">donna@calvaryaustin.org</link>
<br></br>
<br></br>
<br></br>

<p>back to ....<link href="../about/staff.html">Meet Our Staff</link></p>
</content>
