<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
	Donna Cano Bio - Part of the Staff Bios

	$Id: james.xml,v 1.4 2004/08/23 21:20:39 premav Exp $

-->

<content title="Brief Bio of James Lazono">
<heading>Meet James Lazono</heading>
<br></br>
<br></br>
<br></br>
<br></br>
<img src="../images/staff/jamesweb.jpg" alt="James Lazono"/>
<heading>Spouse</heading>
<p>Vicky</p>

<heading>Children</heading>
<p>Andreana, Jonathan, Juliana</p>

<heading>Very Brief Testimony</heading>
<p>God had been knocking on my door for 25 years, but my pride would not let Him in.  Finally, during my freshman year in 1992 at UT in Austin, I did the most difficult thing I had ever done in my whole life.  I swallowed my pride and answered the door and trusted in this God man they called Jesus Christ.  My life has not been the same since not because of my doing but because of His.  I was once blind but now I see.</p>

<heading>Favorite Book of the Bible and Why</heading>
<p>James. Need I say more?  In seriousness, this was one of the first books I studied when I became a Christian, so it's kind of sentimental to me and just helped me establish strong roots in my relationship with our Lord.</p>

<heading>Favorite Verse and Why</heading>
<p>2 Corinthians 12:9. This is my favorite verse because it reminds me in time of weakness that that is where God does His perfect work.</p>

<heading>Favorite Book (besides the Bible) and Why</heading>
<p>The Invisible War by Donald Barnhouse.  This is one of my favorites along with Mere Christianity by C.S. Lewis.  I really enjoyed this book because of Donald Barnhouse's insight on the things not seen particularly in regards to spiritual warfare.  If you are not motivated to put on the full armor of God, you will be after reading this book.</p>

<heading>Who do you most admire (besides Jesus)</heading>
<p>The Apostle Paul. I admire Paul for his tenacity, steadfastness and his love for the Lord. I also admire his desire and compassion to minister to others.  But, the one I relate to better is Moses.  He did not feel equipped but God equipped him and used him in such a mighty way.</p>

<heading>What do you do at Calvary</heading>
<p>Elder-currently teaching New Believer's class.</p>

<br/>
<br/>
Mail me at <link href="mailto:jvlozano@austin.rr.com">jvlozano@austin.rr.com</link>

<br></br>
<br></br>
<br></br>

<p>back to ....<link href="../about/staff.html">Meet Our Staff</link></p>
</content>
