<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
	Donna Cano Bio - Part of the Staff Bios

	$Id: jason.xml,v 1.2 2004/07/08 00:58:42 premav Exp $

-->

<content title="Brief Bio of Jason Moore">
<heading>Meet Jason Moore</heading>
<br></br>
<br></br>
<br></br>
<br></br>
<img src="../images/staff/jasonweb.jpg" alt="Jason Moore"/>
<heading>Spouse</heading>
<p>Elizabeth</p>

<heading>Children</heading>
<p>Sean, Joshua, and Sara</p>

<heading>Very Brief Testimony</heading>
<p>I prayed to receive salvation when I was about 13 years old in the little church that my grandmother attended for years. I say about 13, because I really don't remember how old I was, and nothing in my life really changed to provide any evidence of the change. When I was 18, my mother gave me a New International Version of the Bible for my birthday.  Before that I had only had a Revised Standard Version (the closest thing to Greek you could ever call English!).  I decided that if I called myself a Christian, I should at least try to read through the Bible once to get an idea what it said.  I found my new NIV bible very readable.  As I read, the Holy Spirit worked changes in my life.  I don't know when the "moment" of my salvation was (except before the foundation of the world), but I see Christ's work in my life now, and thank Him for all He has done for me.</p>

<heading>Favorite Book of the Bible and Why</heading>
<p>Proverbs - because I have a short attention span, and there is some much practical information that can be gathered very quickly from the Book of Proverbs. My second favorite is Habakkuk - just to be different.  I like the poetic and prophetic depiction of waiting on the Lord.</p>

<heading>Favorite Verse and Why</heading>
<p>Proverbs 10:19 is the one I probably quote the most as a
reminder to myself: "When words are many, sin is not absent, but he who holds his tongue is wise" NIV).</p>

<heading>Favorite Book (besides the Bible) and Why</heading>
<p>Probably my favorite book is The Restaurant at the End of the Universe from the Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy series. Sorry, not very spiritual, but a highly amusing read!  There's nothing wrong with a good laugh. (Proverbs 17:22)</p>

<heading>Who do you most admire (besides Jesus)</heading>
<p>There are some many people who have influenced my life or done great things that I really can't pick. I admire different people for different things. I admire Hudson Taylor and George Mueller for their faith. I admire my wife for her energy. And many others...</p>

<heading>What do you do at Calvary</heading>
<p>I oversee the team that put together and is teaching the Calvary Discipleship Program 201 class.  I am also a Hall Monitor in the children's ministry (now that's fun!)</p>

<br></br>
<br></br>
<br></br>

<p>back to ....<link href="../about/staff.html">Meet Our Staff</link></p>
</content>
