<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
	Donna Cano Bio - Part of the Staff Bios

	$Id: jeremy.xml,v 1.2 2004/07/08 00:58:57 premav Exp $

-->

<content title="Brief Bio of Jeremy Valencia">
<heading>Meet Jeremy Valencia</heading>
<br></br>
<br></br>
<br></br>
<br></br>

<img src="../images/staff/jeremyweb.jpg" alt="Jeremy Valencia"/>

<heading>Spouse</heading>
<p>Single</p>

<heading>Children</heading>
<p>None</p>

<heading>Very Brief Testimony</heading>
<p>Was a sinner, now a saint (you said brief). Seriously though, I grew up in church all my life, had great Christian parents, but I never had a personal relationship with Christ.  I took what little I knew about God and the Bible and tested it to life.  I was a pleasure seeker and ultimately was not fulfilled in the world.  I found out how much I didn't measure up to God's standard when I started reading the bible.  I gave my life to Christ on August 31, 1999 after reading some scripture.  <br/>
                        I went church seeking, and even visited Calvary Chapel, but decided since I was so "church" cultured, not to attend church immediately.  I grew a little and when I was ready, a friend invited me to Calvary.  It was almost a year to the date since I last visited. I liked the Bible study and knew this is where God wanted me.</p>

<heading>Favorite Book of the Bible and Why</heading>
<p>Psalms - The Psalmist goes through real struggles and really expresses and experiences God in a way that is real to me. It speaks to me when I'm in tribulations and it encourages me through them.</p>

<heading>Favorite Verse and Why</heading>
<p>Philippians 1:21 For to me to live is Christ, and to die is gain. <br/>
                        It's my favorite because it is so focused. It's a mentality I wish to be consistent in, and   yet fall short so many times. But man... to be able to live that verse is awesome.</p>

<heading>Favorite Book (besides the Bible) and Why</heading>
<p>The Next Generation Leader by Andy Stanley, because it is so encouraging and practical at the same time.</p>

<heading>Who do you most admire (besides Jesus)</heading>
<p>Dead: Oswald Chambers. Living: My Dad.</p>

<heading>What do you do at Calvary</heading>
<p>Multi Media Ministry Leader</p>

<br></br>
<br></br>
<br></br>

<p>back to ....<link href="../about/staff.html">Meet Our Staff</link></p>
</content>
