<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
	Donna Cano Bio - Part of the Staff Bios

	$Id: katherine.xml,v 1.2 2004/07/08 00:59:12 premav Exp $

-->

<content title="Brief Bio of Katherine E. Nogues">
<heading>Meet Katherine Nogues</heading>
<br></br>
<br></br>
<br></br>
<br></br>

<img src="../images/staff/katherineweb.jpg"/>

<heading>Spouse</heading>
<p>Single</p>

<heading>Children</heading>
<p>2 Siamese cats: Honey &amp; Lo Mein (like the noodle).</p>

<heading>Very Brief Testimony</heading>
<p>I had attended a traditional protestant church all my life, but only really to please my parents.  When I left for college, I was away from the authority that had kept me from doing those stupid things.  I indulged, and after disappointments, divorce, and many bad decisions God had me meet someone who invited me to a church that loved God and taught His ways.  After only a few weeks God brought me to the point of knowing that the many self-centered decisions I had made would continue unless I turned my life over to Him.  I clearly heard Him say to me at one of the alter calls, "Stand up, this may be your last chance." I needed Him.  I stood up and asked Jesus to take control of my decisions and my life.  At that point my entire life changed.  The bible became alive to me. I could see me in so many of the people and parables.  With every decision I submitted to God, I found far more than I could've ever dreamed given to me.  He sent me to far off places to proclaim His name and His forgiving grace through song and prayer.  I clearly see His hand in every position He has placed me in, spring-boarding me into the next. God continues to teach me and break those little bad habits that still linger.  He alone brings the healing forgiveness that I need. His name alone be praised for His abounding love and grace!</p>

<heading>Favorite Book of the Bible and Why</heading>
<p>Proverbs-because God reveals so much of how He wants me to live through the verses.</p>

<heading>Favorite Verse and Why</heading>
<p>Proverbs 9:10 "The fear of the Lord is the beginning of wisdom, and knowledge of the Holy One is understanding."  I have seen in my own life and in others that have built a relationship with the Lord become wise as the Lord opens our eyes to see the folly and lies of this world. It's a good thing!</p>

<heading>Favorite Book (besides the Bible) and Why</heading>
<p>Hudson Taylor's Spiritual Secret This is one of the books that had the greatest impact for me as a new believer. It helped me to see the extent of trust that God wants me to have in Him.</p>

<heading>Who do you most admire (besides Jesus)</heading>
<p>>I would have to say the Burke's in our own church family.  I see Andy and Toni striving to do what God wants in every situation. Because of their faithfulness, even in the toughest situations, I have seen God bless their marriage and their family.  God answers their prayers in amazing ways that can't help but impact those around them, believers and unbelievers alike. </p>

<heading>What do you do at Calvary</heading>
<p>My role at Calvary is to be a conduit for God to move and work through. I am to be supportive and connective. Gentle as a dove, wise as a serpent. I am to be flexible, careful, trusting, and protective.</p>

<br></br>
<br></br>
<br></br>

<p>back to ....<link href="../about/staff.html">Meet Our Staff</link></p>
</content>
