<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
	Donna Cano Bio - Part of the Staff Bios

	$Id: matt.xml,v 1.4 2004/08/24 03:15:33 tie Exp $

-->

<content title="Brief Bio of Matt Lang">
<heading>Meet Matt Lang</heading>
<br></br>
<br></br>
<br></br>
<br></br>
<img src="../images/staff/mattweb.jpg" alt="Matt Lang"/>
<heading>Spouse</heading>
<p>Tammy</p>

<heading>Children</heading>
<p>Mara, Micah and Macy</p>

<heading>Very Brief Testimony</heading>
<p>I grew up going to church and was saved at age 11. I really didn't have a true relationship with God until college though. I would attend church, youth group and camps, but never knew God. In college, around the time I started dating Tammy, I got into the Word and that all changed.</p>

<heading>Favorite Book of the Bible and Why</heading>
<p>Ephesians, because it's so applicable to my life. I know what I have in Christ, and it gives practical ways to live out my faith.</p>

<heading>Favorite Verse and Why</heading>
<p>I really like Jason Moore's, but would have to say it's: Micah 6:8, partly because I named my son that, but it gives us all that God requires of us.</p>

<heading>Favorite Book (besides the Bible) and Why</heading>
<p>The Last Battle by CS Lewis. It's the final book in the Lion, Witch and the Wardrobe series. I liked the way it ended, that even though the place they loved was destroyed, there was a much better place they were going. It reminds me of where our final destination is.</p>

<heading>Who do you most admire (besides Jesus)</heading>
<p>I would have to say my mom because of all the sacrifice she's made in her life for me and my brother and her Godly influence.</p>

<heading>What do you do at Calvary</heading>
<p>Recently I've changed roles from overseeing the greeting ministry to overseeing the facilities and service ministries. I get to work closely with Johnny Arnold and Jim Curbow. I'm really excited about this new opportunity. I'm also leading a Home Fellowship group in Pflugerville.</p>

<br/>
<br/>
Mail me at <link href="mailto:tammyl91@swbell.net">tammyl91@swbell.net</link>
<br></br>
<br></br>
<br></br>

<p>back to ....<link href="../about/staff.html">Meet Our Staff</link></p>
</content>
