<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
	Donna Cano Bio - Part of the Staff Bios

	$Id: mike.xml,v 1.2 2004/07/08 01:15:17 premav Exp $

-->

<content title="Brief Bio of Mike Hardcastle">
<heading>Meet Mike Hardcastle</heading>
<br></br>
<br></br>
<br></br>
<br></br>
<img src="../images/staff/mikeweb.xml" alt="Mike Hardcastle"/>
<heading>Spouse</heading>
<p>Elizabeth</p>

<heading>Children</heading>
<p>Caleb, David, &amp; Nathan</p>

<heading>Very Brief Testimony</heading>
<p>I was saved as a youth while living in the Houston area.  I didn't walk with the Lord and was pretty rebellious. When I went away to college, I didn't want to attend church and wanted to declare my freedom from attending with my mom.  In the later years of college, I began to feel empty and a desire to return back to the Lord, after trying most of what the world has to offer.  A friend and I tried out a local church and got plugged in, and that is where I rededicated my life to the Lord, and first felt the call to full-time ministry.  I also met my wife there.  I graduated and moved to Austin and started working for Emerson Electric.  I got married a year later and we were blessed with 3 boys over the years.  We were attending an Independent Baptist church for most of this time, and heavily involved in the leadership.  We left that church in 1999-2000 and attended Calvary Austin and were hooked from the start.  It was our first exposure to a Calvary, and we loved it.  We have served in various capacities here over the last few years, and accepted a position in December 2003 as Executive Director, leaving Corporate America and a 15 year career behind with little thought, knowing it was God's calling in our lives.</p>

<heading>Favorite Book of the Bible and Why</heading>
<p>Psalms-I can't help but be brought into worship when I read it.</p>

<heading>Favorite Verse and Why</heading>
<p>Galatians 6:9, It is a promise to overcome and succeed if we will not give up and continue to wait upon the Lord.</p>

<heading>Favorite Book (besides the Bible) and Why</heading>
<p>Ordering Your Private World by Gordon MacDonald.  It is a good review of our priorities and spiritual world, to make sure that we are balanced and don't crumble in this world.</p>

<heading>Who do you most admire (besides Jesus)</heading>
<p>Andrew Murray-He seemed to have such a grasp on prayer and a relationship with the Lord, and I aspire to follow in his shoes and have that type of relationship with Christ and understanding of spiritual things.</p>

<heading>What do you do at Calvary</heading>
<p>I am the Executive Director, overseeing the church staff and administration.</p>

<br></br>
<br></br>
<br></br>

<p>back to ....<link href="../about/staff.html">Meet Our Staff</link></p>
</content>
