<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<content title="Calvary Kids Purpose">
  <subheading>Our Four Part Purpose: Love, Serve, Teach, and Encourage</subheading>

  <subheading>Love</subheading>
  <p>Jesus took the time to be with children and told us, "Do not hinder them from coming to me, for the kingdom of heaven belongs to such as these". We, the teachers, represent Jesus in our classrooms to the children. Every child should experience His love through us when we greet them at the door, relate with them during class, see them depart for home, and have contact with them outside of class.</p>

  <subheading>Serve</subheading>
  <p>"So when He had washed their feet, taken His garments, and sat down again, He said to them, 'Do you know what I have done to you? You call me Teacher and Lord, and you say well for so I am. If I then, your Lord and Teacher, have washed your feet, you also ought to wash one another's feet. For I have given you an example, that you should do as I have done to you.'" ~ John 13:12-15</p>

  <p>Teachers will be examples of servants to our children, then let our children be servants. When we allow our classes to help us, we are teaching and training them how to serve. We will use every opportunity possible to involve our classes in service.</p>

  <subheading>Teach</subheading>
  <p>Parallel to Deuteronomy 6:5-9:</p>

  <p>You shall love the Lord your God will all your heart and with all your soul and with all your might. And these words, which I am commanding you today, shall be on your heart; and you shall teach them diligently to your children and shall talk of them when you sit in your classroom and when you walk in the hallways and when you greet them and when you say good-bye. And you shall bind them as a sign on your hand and they shall be as fontanels on your forehead. And you shall write them on the doorway of your classroom and on your bulletin boards and chalkboards.</p>

  <subheading>Encourage</subheading>
  <p>We desire to encourage our children in the classroom setting by being positive and being messengers of hope. We like to set up our classes for success by centering all the teaching and activities around the child's age appropriateness. We set up high standards for class control, and patiently instill these standards into our students. We look for opportunities to listen to the children's needs and concerns so that we can pray effectively for them as well as offer help and encouragement to our families.</p>

  <p>We want our ministry to be one that lives out what Paul the Apostle admonishes us to do, "Let us consider one another in order to stir up love and good works, not forsaking the assembling of ourselves together, as is the manner of some, but exhorting one another, and so much more as you see the Day approaching." ~ Hebrews 10:24-25.</p>

</content>
