<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<content title="Serve with Calvary Kids">
  <strong>Serve with Us</strong>
  <p>We desire for you to bless our kids and be blessed by service to them as the Lord leads you. There is ALWAYS an opportunity for service in our ever growing kids ministry! Below is a thorough explanation of the application process to become a kids ministry worker. A list of <a href="openings.html">current openings</a> is also available.</p>
  <p>Calvary Austin has developed an exhaustive Children's Ministry worker screening process. We feel strongly that, in today's world, it is wise to confront the growing and disturbing problem of child abuse within the church and to implement appropriate policies to protect our children and church from harm. These policies also include only allowing workers to serve after they have been attending Calvary Chapel Austin a minimum of six months, as well as ensuring that all volunteers work in pairs.</p>  <p>From the time a person first becomes interested in becoming a Children's Ministry volunteer - in whatever capacity (teacher, hall monitor, worship leader, etc.) - to the point that they are trained and placed in a classroom, here are the steps along the way.</p>
  <heading>1. Attend an Orientation</heading>
  <p>Orientation is the very first step in the process, before any paperwork is filled out or schedules are made. At Orientation, you will hear about our vision, CM policies, the different ministry positions available, etc. You will also have an opportunity to meet the leadership and ask any questions you may have. Jesus told his disciples to "count the cost" and we want all potential volunteers to be able to do likewise when it comes to taking on a role within our ministry. You will walk away knowing what we expect of you and what you can expect of us. Those who wish to continue on in the process will be able to fill out the necessary paperwork (see step #2) at the Orientation meeting. We aim to hold orientations on an as-needed basis. </p>
  <heading>2. Complete a CM Application Packet and Background Check Consent Form</heading>
  <p>Absolutely no workers will be allowed to serve without a processed and cleared application on file. We take our children's ministry safety very seriously, and we know you would agree! The application is thorough and we ask that you be diligent in answering all questions. Please treat it as you would any job application. We realize that some questions are sensitive and/or private, and we assure you that your confidentiality will be maintained every step of the way. Please contact a <a href="contact.html">ministry leader</a> if you have any questions or concerns about the application.</p>
  <heading>3. Criminal Background Check and References</heading>
  <p>After you turn in your application packet, we will contact your references and conduct the Criminal Background Check. A criminal history does not necessarily exclude you from service, but we may want to further discuss your history during the interview, if we feel it is relevant to our ministry. This background/reference check phase is the most lengthy and may take up to two to three weeks. </p>
  <heading>4. Interview with CM Service Leader</heading>
  <p>We will schedule you for a brief meeting with the service leader who presides over the service in which you would like to serve. </p>
  <heading>5. Make Contact with Coordinator</heading>
  <p>After your interview, your service leader will refer you to the coordinator for the specific age group with which you want to serve. It is the coordinator who will be able to arrange your training and talk with you about scheduling.</p>
  <p>That's it! We know it may look quite involved, and it is, because that's how much we value our children, and how important it is to us to be good stewards and protect our church from liability issues. What a witness to the world to go above and beyond in this area!</p>
  
</content>
