<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<content title="Calvary Kids Sunday">
  <subheading>Schedule and Class Locations</subheading>
  <p>Calvary Kids offers age appropriate nursery, preschool, and elementary Sunday school classes for children ages 0 through 5th grade during all services at  8:00 a.m., 9:45 a.m., and 11:30 a.m. You may begin signing your children into their classrooms fifteen minutes before each service time. </p>

  <p>The Calvary Kids hallway is easy to find! After entering through the front of the church, walk straight ahead past the media ministry, youth room, and events center. A giant purple octopus on your left signals that you have arrived in the kids ministry area!</p>

  <p>Due to differences in class sizes, locations of classes vary slightly depending on the service you attend. Calvary Kids volunteers, as well as signage in the hallway, will help you find the appropriate classroom for your child.</p>

  <subheading>Auditorium Setting for Services</subheading>
  <p>Our services in the main auditorium are designed for adults, so we ask that you take your children to the classes offered in the Calvary Kids ministry. The adult services are taught at an adult level, therefore, just as you would not expect your child to sit with you through a high school or college class, the adult services at Calvary Chapel are for adults and not children. We provide age appropriate classes for the children not only for their sake, but to allow their parents to be undistracted, strengthened and encouraged at an adult level as well. </p>

  <subheading>New Parents Room and Nursing Moms Room</subheading>
  <p>Audio and video are provided in the New Parents Room where parents can sit with their children and see and participate in the service. As you enter through the front of the church, the New Parents Room will be located on your left, just past the Events Center.</p>

  <p>For mothers who are nursing, a Nursing Moms Room is provided where you can see the service through a one way window and hear the worship and teaching over a speaker system. Entry to the Nursing Moms Room is through the ladies restroom. Calvary Kids volunteers will be happy to help you find the Nursing Moms Room.</p>

</content>
