<?xml version = "1.0" encoding = "UTF-8"?>
<preface>
	<title>About Docbook</title>
        <para>Note: This is a short overview about how this document was put together.</para>
	<para>The approach of writing documentation in HTML was inheretly problem infested. The content was "polluted" with
HTML presentational tags and such impossible to convert to any other view. Another big issue was <![CDATA[L&F 
consistency. Despite the explicit instruction of which HTML tags to use, authors couldn't keep up with all complexities 
and issue faced when writing HTML documents. Documents were also hard to shuffle around in a document book thus 
leading to a very big maintance costs]]></para>
	<para>After some considerate time spent looking around, we came to the conclusion that Docbook initiative is the most
reasonable way to go. DocBook is a XML/SGML DTD that lets authors in technical groups concentrate on the organization 
and meaning of the documents they write.</para>
	<para>Docbook XML DTD ,which we are using, has accompanying XSL stylesheets that allow us to define different views of 
Docbook-ed XML content i.e., all the presentation issues are solved through XSL stylesheets. These stylesheets are 
very flexible, well maintained, and allow easily customized hooks for specialized home-brewed styles of views.</para>
	<para>Simply put, you have xml tagged content, detached from any fomatting issues, chunked into logical pieces, which 
are then easily (re)arranged, put together, and in the end XSL stylesheet is applied against it to create any 
kind of presentational view.</para>
	<para>Docbook DTD's are maintained by independent consortium - <ulink url = "http://www.oasis-open.org">
			<citetitle>OASIS</citetitle>
		</ulink>. 
The principal maintainer of Docbook is <ulink url = "http://www.nwalsh.com">
			<citetitle>Norman Walsh</citetitle>
		</ulink> , a member of 
XSL working group, Sun Microsystems employee.</para>
	<para>Although Docbook DTD is very big, 300 + elements, the learning curve is very steep, and most of the time not more 
than 50 elements are used.  This <ulink url = "http://www.caldera.de/~eric/crash-course/HTML">
			<citetitle>article</citetitle>
		</ulink>is suitable for a first contact with Docbook. A good reference that you might want to use can be found <ulink url = "http://www.docbook.org/tdg/en/html/docbook.html">
			<citetitle>here</citetitle>
		</ulink>. 
There is also a <ulink url = "http://developer.arsdigita.com/doc/docbook-primer.html"><citetitle>very brief introduction</citetitle></ulink> with references to tools such as Emacs with PSGML.
	</para>
	<formalpara>
		<title>Docbook documentation guidelines</title>
		<para>
		<itemizedlist>
		<listitem><para>Format for readability and content, not for a formated document.</para> 
		<para>It is not your job and responsibility to make sure the final documentation looks good. If you use appropriate markup 
		tags for the content of your documentation, Docbook will ensure that your document looks good. Do not substitute an inappropriate
		DocBook XML tag because you do not like the "look" of the correct tag.</para> 
                  
		</listitem>

		<listitem>
		<para>Do what you can to ensure you turn in a valid DocBook file.</para> 

       		<para>If you notice any parser errors during documentation build, correct them to ensure XML validity. If you get absolutely stuck notify
	        one of the documentation leads. The reviewers will correct any DocBook errors you create, but please try to reduce the number of errors.
		</para>	
		</listitem>	
		<listitem>
                <para>All <![CDATA[<chapter> and major <section> ]]> tags must have an id attribute. The id must be all lower case, with dashes seperating 
		words: <![CDATA[ <section id="configuring-containerinvoker"> ]]>
		</para>

		<para>This is very important since it allows other documentation writers to refer to your chapters and sections</para>	
		</listitem>	
		<listitem>
		<para>
               	When trying to decide between an ordered and unordered list, simply ask yourself the following question: "Does the order of the 
		listed items matter?" or "If I change the order of the listed items, does that change the meaning of the list?". If you answer "No" 
		to either question, then an unordered list is likely the logical choice.</para>
		</listitem>
                
                <listitem>
		<para>
		When referring to chapters, sections, code samples, figures and other parts of documentation use either <![CDATA[<link> or <xref>]]> 
		element. </para>

		<para><![CDATA[<xref> ]]> element is more powerful since it creates both link and link text. You should use it whenever possible.</para>
		<para>For example: If there is a figure somewhere in the documentation <![CDATA[<figure id="comp.ejb-jar.xml">]]> then using 
		<![CDATA[<xref linkend="comp.ejb-jar.xml"/>]]> creates both the link to that figure as well as link text. Link text is usually
		autogenerated (in case of figures - figure number) or assigned by the author of that link target.</para>
                  
                <para><![CDATA[<link>]]> element also creates links, but you assign link text.  For example:
		<![CDATA[<link linkend="jca-terminology">JCA Terminology</link>]]></para>
			
                </listitem>

		<listitem>
		<para>Use <![CDATA[<ulink>]]> element to create links to other URLs. For example:
		<![CDATA[<ulink url="http://java.sun.com/j2se/1.3/docs/guide/rmi/rmisocketfactory.doc.html">The Custom Socket Factory Tutorial</ulink>]]>
		</para>
		</listitem>
		</itemizedlist>	
	</para>
	</formalpara>
	
</preface>
