<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- 

	Calvary Live
	
	$Id: live.xml,v 1.5 2003/03/03 00:15:50 javajames27 Exp $
		
-->
<content title="Calvary Live" base=".">

	<welcome>
		<p>Join us every Sunday morning and Wednesday evening for our live webcast. You may watch, using RealVideo®, during the times 	listed below. Be sure to pick up a copy (by clicking on the icon below) of the RealPlayer; it's way cool! When you're ready to go, click on the 	Live button below to join us at our home in Austin, Texas.</p>
		<subtext>Our RealVideo is a G2 stream. This means that you need a recent version of the RealPlayer, and that you can watch over a 	28K modem, 56K modem, or cable modem or DSL connection. </subtext>
		<note>Note that we are currently experiencing difficulties with live feeds. The video archive will be available no later than 24 hours after the initial broadcast using the links at the bottom of this page. Thanks for your understanding and prayers.</note>
	</welcome>
	
	 <broadcasts>
	 	<broadcast>Sunday, 11:30 AM CDT</broadcast>
	 	<broadcast>Wednesday, 7:00 PM CDT</broadcast>
		     <sidetext>Note that this link is only active during the live webcast. During non-service times the RealPlayer will report an error.</sidetext> 
	 </broadcasts>
	
     <video-archives>
		<p>If you've missed the live webcast you can view recent services here. We archive the 2 most recent Sunday and Wednesday 	RealVideos; click on one of the links below to watch.</p>
	</video-archives>
	
	<broadcast-archive>
	 	<broadcast href="http://www.calvarychapel.org/austin/video/sunday.ram">Most recent Sunday</broadcast>
	 	<broadcast href="http://www.calvarychapel.org/austin/video/sundaylast.ram">Sunday 2 weeks ago</broadcast>
	 	<broadcast href="http://www.calvarychapel.org/austin/video/wednesday.ram">Most recent Wednesday</broadcast>
	 	<broadcast href="http://www.calvarychapel.org/austin/video/wednesdaylast.ram">Wednesday 2 weeks ago</broadcast>
	</broadcast-archive>
	
	<audio-archives>
		<p>A large number of the messages are available in Real Audio® format. Visit the <link href="../msgs/msgsAudioArchive.html">Audio Archives</link> for a list of available messages.</p>
	</audio-archives>
	
</content>