<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?> 
<!-- 

        Free Indeed (Addictions) Ministry  - The ministry and its detail 
        
	   $Id: freeindeed.xml,v 1.9 2004/07/13 20:18:08 tie Exp $ 
                
--> 
<content title="Free Indeed"> 
        <ministry id="freeindeed"> 
                <name>Free Indeed (Addictions) Ministry</name> 
                <overview>Our purpose: The puprose of Calvary Free Indeed is to honor and glorify God through our outreach to the church and community. We want to provide hope and freedom to those that are struggling with habitual sin (substance abuse, pornography, overeating, smoking, sexual impurity) and give them an understanding of the foundational truths that God has given us that are the means to being free from addictions.</overview>

                <long-description> 
                        <p><strong>"So if the Son sets you free, you will be free indeed." -- John 8:36</strong></p> 
						<p><strong>Our Vision: The vision is to use the gospel of Jesus Christ in teaching those that are struggling with habitual sin about the freedom found in Jesus Christ. We use our resources to reach as many as possible to share, in grace, the foundational truth found in God's Word apart from those methods used by worldly wisdom or methodologies.</strong></p>
						<p>First and foremost, we must tell you that God's grace is able to help you overcome any sin, and there is hope for you. Calvary Austin's Free Indeed ministry is an extension of the <link href="http://www.settingcaptivesfree.com/home/">Setting Captives Free</link> ministry that was started by Mike Cleveland. This program offers web based courses that will help you to understand the addiction or habitual sin nature of man. The courses allow you to see why habitual sin is wrong and the steps necessary to live a life that glorifies God. This program provides an excellent foundation for us to teach and equip you to be able to claim that you are "Free Indeed." The Free Indeed program at Calvary is based on people who have experienced these problems themselves and understand your fear, shame, lonliness, and struggles.</p>
						<p>It is our desire to provide a mentor, if possible, for the specific program you would like to take. If one is available, we can assign a mentor from Calvary Austin. If one is not currently available from Calvary Austin, one will be assigned for you by Setting Captives Free. Once you have enrolled and been assigned a mentor for the course, we can assign an accountability partner at Calvary Austin. The difference is that a mentor has been trained to take you through the course, whereas the accountability partner will be somebody from our chruch that will read your course responses and pray for you. It is our desire to see you "Free Indeed" and gain the life and fulfillment that God wants us to have in our relationship with him. Please do not start a Setting Captives Free online course before you contact us if you wish to have a mentor or accountability partner from Calvary Austin.</p>

<!--                        <p>First and foremost, we must tell you that God's grace is able to help you overcome any sin, and there is hope for you.  Our approach to dealing with these addictions is to partner with an online program made available through <link href="http://www.settingcaptivesfree.com/home/">Setting Captives Free</link>.  We direct you to their web page for the particular topic and study program, but also provide you local support and accountability.  The below links will connect you with their web page where you can read about the particular programs.  They will assign you a mentor, but you can also copy someone as an accountability partner.  If you don't already have an accountability partner in Calvary, we will provide you one, and we ask that you include the appropriate email below in the cc field at the bottom of your day one study.  This will forward your day 1 study to the accountability coordinator who will assign your accountability partner.  Your personal accountability partner will contact you immediately to provide you support.</p>
-->    
             <p>Calvary's Free Indeed (CFI) Accountability for Men: <link href="mailto:cfi_male@calvaryaustin.org">cfi_male@calvaryaustin.org</link></p> 
     		<p>Calvary's Free Indeed (CFI) Accountability for Women: <link href="mailto:cfi_female@calvaryaustin.org">cfi_female@calvaryaustin.org</link></p> 

		

      <heading>Courses</heading> 
      <p> <link href="http://www.settingcaptivesfree.com/course/">Pure Freedom - Sexual Impurity</link></p>
      <p> <link href="http://www.settingcaptivesfree.com/spouses/">A United Front - For Wives of Addicts</link></p>
      <p> <link href="http://www.settingcaptivesfree.com/purity_force/">Purity Force - Maintaining Teen Purity</link></p>
      <p> <link href="http://www.settingcaptivesfree.com/lords_table/">Lord's Table - Overeating</link></p>
      <p> <link href="http://www.settingcaptivesfree.com/door_hope/">Door of Hope - Homosexuality</link></p>
      <p> <link href="http://www.settingcaptivesfree.com/breath_life/">Breath of Life - Smoking</link></p>
      <p> <link href="http://www.settingcaptivesfree.com/new_wine/">New Wine - Alcoholism</link></p>
      <heading>Testimonies</heading> 
      <p> Here are some<link href="../ministries/testimonies.html"> testimonies</link> of people who have been helped by this ministry</p>

	<heading>Interested in joining the Free Indeed ministry team?</heading>
	<p>Email one of the appropriate accountability accounts below:</p>
                 <p>Calvary's Free Indeed (CFI) Accountability for Men: <link href="mailto:cfi_male@calvaryaustin.org">cfi_male@calvaryaustin.org</link></p> 
     		<p>Calvary's Free Indeed (CFI) Accountability for Women: <link href="mailto:cfi_female@calvaryaustin.org">cfi_female@calvaryaustin.org</link></p> 

    </long-description> 
     <contacts>
	  	<contact-email email="todd@equiptheword.com">Todd Ellsworth</contact-email>
	  	<contact-phone phone="671-8298">Contact Phone</contact-phone>
   	  </contacts>           
                <ministry-logo>../images/ministries/freeindeed1.jpg</ministry-logo> 
        </ministry> 
</content> 
