<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<!-- 

        The internet ministry's vision
        
        $Id: internet-vision.xml,v 1.2 2002/11/17 04:10:05 javajames27 Exp $
                
-->
<content title="Calvary Austin Internet Ministry Vision" base=".">
  <heading>Internet Ministry Vision</heading>
  <subheading>Our Mission</subheading>
  <p>The mission of the Calvary Internet Ministry extends the Calvary
    Chapel Austin mission statement to the internet:</p>
  <p>We are committed to execute the church’s vision of "win, equip, and send" by empowering every
    ministry with Internet technologies.</p>
  <subheading>Our Vision</subheading>
  <p>The Internet Ministry is an extension of every member and ministry in the Calvary Austin
    church body.</p>
  <subheading>Execution</subheading>
  <p>Over the next few months, the Internet ministry will be constructing a toolset from a variety
    of existing frameworks and tools to enable each ministry to edit their own content. A longer term
    goal is to extend these tools to allow ministries to perform more administrative tasks, such as
    goal tracking, self-maintained mailing lists, and event management. In parallel to this effort,
    work will be done to extend our current web site offering to visitors through the use of current
    technologies like Flash presentations, discussion forums, and other mechanisms that enable others
    to learn more about our church and the Christian faith.</p>
  <subheading>Helping</subheading>
  <p>There are quite a few ways that you can help with the internet ministry. Above all, your
    prayers and encouragement are always needed, as the Internet is a battleground that has continual
    spirtual battles. In addition, you may wish to pray and seek God's guidance to join our ministry
    in a more dedicated basis. Some of the help we need and are willing to train includes:</p>

  <list>
    <item>Anyone who knows how to perform
      basic computer operations, such as creating, editing, and
      copying files, for content management of this web
      site.</item>
    <item>Editors who can perform checks for grammar, assemble content for the homepage and other areas
      of the site, and assist with overall content management.</item>
    <item>We also need help from people who know or are willing to
      learn any of the following technologies: XML, XSL, Java, Java Servlets/JSP, database
      technologies, and HTML/Javascript.</item>
  </list>
  <p>To learn how to serve, contact the web servant team at:
    <link href="mailto:webservant-austin@calvarychapel.org">Web Servant Team</link></p>
  
</content>
