<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<!-- 

        The internet ministry's vision
        
        $Id: internet-vision.xml,v 1.5 2003/06/03 16:38:56 javajames27 Exp $
                
-->
<content title="Calvary Austin Internet Ministry Vision" base=".">
  <heading>Internet Ministry Vision</heading>
  <subheading>Our Mission</subheading>
  <p>The Calvary Austin Internet Ministry is committed to the presentation of the Gospel of Jesus, edification of the church body, and ministering to the lost and hurting through the use of innovative Internet technologies in a professional and compelling manner.</p>
  <subheading>Our Vision</subheading>
  <p>Every visitor to the Calvary Austin Web Site is given the gospel message, an opportunity for edification, and the ability to minister to others in need. This is accomplished by every servant of the local church body through the use of multimedia presentations, articles, forums, and other technologies. The Internet Ministry is an extension of every member and ministry in the Calvary Austin church body, enabling them to reach those previously unreachable beyond the local church attendees.</p>
  <subheading>Execution</subheading>
  <p>The Internet Ministry has a continuing goal to be one of the most innovative web sites on the Internet. This means that we will lead Calvary Chapel, Christian, and secular web sites in the professional and appropriate use of innovative web technologies. We will utilize these technologies to the utmost for spreading the gospel, edification of Christ's church, and assisting those in need of ministering. Our web site will be accessible from version 4 and newer web browsers, offer fast downloading and high bandwidth multimedia viewing options, and will be friendly to the visually disabled. The Internet Ministry is resolved to make this happen by God's provision of time and talent to the ministry. As always, work will continue to be done to extend our current web site content to visitors through the use of current technologies like Flash presentations, discussion forums, news articles, streaming audio/video content, as well as others to enable visitors to learn more about our church, the Christian faith, and grow deeper in their walk with Jesus.</p>
  <subheading>Helping</subheading>
  <p>There are quite a few ways that you can help with the internet ministry. Above all, your
    prayers and encouragement are always needed, as the Internet is a battleground that has continual
    spirtual battles. In addition, you may wish to pray and seek God's guidance to join our ministry
    in a more dedicated basis. Some of the help we need and are willing to train includes:</p>

  <list>
    <item>Anyone who knows how to perform
      basic computer operations, such as creating, editing, and
      copying files, for content management of this web
      site.</item>
    <item>Editors who can perform checks for grammar, assemble content for the homepage and other areas
      of the site, and assist with overall content management.</item>
    <item>We also need help from people who know or are willing to
      learn any of the following technologies: XML, XSL, Java, Java Servlets/JSP, database
      technologies, and HTML/Javascript.</item>
  </list>
  <p>To learn how to serve, contact the web servant team at:
    <link href="mailto:webservant-austin@calvarychapel.org">Web Servant Team</link></p>
  
</content>
