<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--

	Free Indeed Ministry- Lord's Table Testimonies

	$Id: lt-male1.xml,v 1.1 2003/12/25 17:47:35 gregk Exp $

-->
<content title="Lord's Table Testimony - Male">
	<ministry id="freeindeed">
	  <name>Lord's Table Testimony - Male</name>
	  <p>I'm a man in my late thirties, who is just an average guy.  I was pretty athletic while growing up, and never had to worry about weight or eating habits.  That is until after college, when my sedentary lifestyle and eating habits caught up with me.  I've slowly gained weight since college, but always wrote it off as being a big guy with a big build. Yes, I knew I was overweight but I didn't think it was by much. Over the last 10 years, I have tried to lose weight by dieting, exercise and formal diet plans.  I have had limited success, but never kept it off.  In the last few years, I reached the high 230's and started to get comments about my weight, eating habits, and lack of self-control.</p>
	  <p>After completing another Setting Captives Free course, the Lord showed me that this was another area of indulging the flesh, and that I needed to deal with it. And after seeing God's power so strong in the other area, I knew He could deliver me here as well.  As I started the study, I struggled with the thought of this problem as an "addiction," but I could admit it was sin (indulging the flesh). Slowly God revealed that it was controlling me instead of Him controlling me, and I was finding fulfillment, or at least trying to, in the pleasure of eating instead of in Him.  Thus, it was idolatry, an addiction, and sin in my life.</p>
	  <p>God has done a work in me, and has enabled me to restore His temple back to the best state of health it's been in since high school. He has further enabled me to find pleasure and fulfillment in Him through His Word, prayer and fellowship, as well as serving others.  I have been able to lose over 35 pounds and have reached my long-term goal of 190-95, and have been able to stay within that range for over a month. God continues to prompt people to ask me about my weight loss and thus give me an opportunity to declare His power and deliverance, and encourage others to seek Him through the SCF studies.  I was even given an opportunity to deliver a Wed. night service at church, in which I spoke of Overcoming Struggles with Sin, outlining the principles I've learned in this journey.  I praise the Lord for his love and deliverance, and encourage others to find this strength in His Word.   TLT Beg. Weight 228, Current Weight 195, Loss 33 pounds. Amen!</p>
      <p> back to ...<link href="../ministries/testimonies.html">Calvary Austin Testimonies</link></p>
   </ministry>
</content>
