<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- 

	Men's Ministry - The ministry and its detail
	
	$Id: men.xml,v 1.15 2004/06/15 16:21:54 tie Exp $
		
-->
<content title="Men's Ministry">
	<ministry id="men">
	  <heading>Men's Ministry Purpose Statement</heading>
<br></br>
	  <p><strong>Unite</strong> men together for the common goal of being <strong>trained</strong> to serve Jesus Christ with every area of their lives, then multiplying our strength by seeking out men to <strong>disciple.</strong></p>
	  <p><strong>Unite, Train, Disciple.</strong></p>
<br></br>
<br></br>
	  <long-description>
	    <heading>Prayer</heading>
<br></br>
	    <p>Each Friday morning (6:00 AM) we invite the men to come pray in the New Parent's room. Enter through the church front door.</p>
<br></br>
	    <heading>Study</heading>
<br></br>
	    <p>The Men's Ministry is about God's word. We desire to see men moved through the power of God's word. There are several Bible Studies scheduled throughout the year. Check the <link href="../calendar/calendar.html">calendar</link> for upcoming meetings.</p>
<br></br>
	    <heading>Accountability</heading>
            <p>Purpose</p>
	    <p>Connect men for the purpose of building servants of God through friendship, accountability, teaching.</p>
            <p>Several Men's Groups are being created across the city. Contact Andy Berke at the email address below to get connected with a group of men in your neighborhood.</p>
	   <heading>Men's Retreat 2004</heading>
       <heading><emphasis>Unite-Train-Disciple</emphasis></heading>
            <p>Oct 15-16 at Camp Tejas. Download a copy of the <link href="http://www.calvarychapel.com/austin/documents/signupsheet.doc">Registration form (Word Document)</link> if you need one.</p>
	    <p><emphasis>WHO:</emphasis>Pastor Art Murillo of The Way Christian Church, Chula Vista, CA, a Calvary Chapel affiliate <link href="http://www.thewaycc.com">(www.thewaycc.com)</link></p>
        <img src="http://www.calvarychapel.org/austin/images/ministries/art.jpg"/>
         <p>Art Murillo was born in Los Angeles to two wonderful Christian parents who loved Jesus with all their heart.  By the time he was 4 years old he  was the “front man” of the family singing group.  He was 6 when he wrote is first worship song. Art spent his childhood and youth evangelizing around the country.</p>

<p>When Art retired from the road at age 19, he chose to seriously pursue higher education and a professional career as a doctor. But before very long, it became clear that his life and career would really be one of complete dedication to the ministry.</p>

<p>Through Art’s adult life he has functioned primarily as Worship Pastor for various ministries.  Today, Art is the Senior Pastor of THE WAY Christian Church in Chula Vista, CA – a suburb of San Diego.  Art is also an American Red Cross Chaplain for the San Diego and Imperial Counties and a sought-after conference speaker and worship leader around the country.</p>

<p>Pastor Art has been married to Rhoda for 17 years and has three young sons. His favorite pastimes include auto racing, well-done steaks and riding his Harley.</p>

        <p><emphasis>WHEN:</emphasis>October 15-16. Event registration starts Friday morning at 7 a.m. You must be signed up by 9:30 a.m. Don't miss the opening worship session with Pastor Murillo!</p>   
        <p><emphasis>WHERE:</emphasis>Camp Tejas<link href="http://www.camptejas.org/tejas/home">(www.camptejas.org)</link> in Giddings, Texas</p>
        <p><emphasis>WHY:</emphasis>To train up the men of our church body through instruction, prayer, small groups and focus groups. Also, to have some awesome time of fellowship and fun!</p>   
        <p><emphasis>BRING:</emphasis>Pillow and sleeping bag (bunk house only), Bible, notebook, pens/pencils, clothing for sporting events, sport equipment, teachable heart.</p>
	    <p><emphasis>TO DO:</emphasis>18 hole Disc golf course, Basketball, Challenge Courses, Climbing wall, Running/Hiking trails, Game room, Horseshoes, Shuffleboard, Tennis, Volleyball. Also, within a 15 minute drive are Mountain Biking Trails and a Paintball gaming location!</p>  
	  </long-description>
	  <contacts>
  	    <contact-email email="calvaryaustinmen@austin.rr.com">Andy Berke</contact-email>
   	  </contacts>
	</ministry>
</content>
