<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--



-->
<content title="New Wine Testimony - Male">
	<ministry id="freeindeed">
	  <name>New Wine Testimony - Male</name>
	  <p>I drank since the time I was a teenager, starting at the age of 16 or 17 years old. During high school and college, I tended to binge drink as stress relief on the weekends. This continued after I graduated from college and began to work with people who drank alcohol to lighten the burden of a stressful job. I respected these co-workers, who were brilliant people, which further reinforced the idea that I could drink and be successful. I headed back to college for a second degree and partied more than I had when I was younger. Once I had graduated, I started an extremely stressful job and fell deeper into my alcoholism. I never did drink in the morning or at work, just at night for stress relief, but deep down I knew I had developed a drinking problem that was fundamentally wrong. I was not a Christian at this point in my life. I felt I had no reason to quit drinking because it was the only thing that I could rely on to numb the pain of the daily stresses of life and to fill the place in my heart for that "something" that was missing.</p>

	  <p>In 1997, I found out my wife was pregnant. This was crushing news to both of us as we had never planned on, nor wanted, children. Ending the pregnancy was not an option for us and we were left with the helpless feeling that we were going to be parents. We were both successful, career-oriented people that wanted to make money and enjoy the fruits of our hard work and kids were not part of that equation. As time passed, I had begun to listen to Calvary Continuum on my drive home from work. Pastor Allen was speaking directly to me every time I listened and I hated the things he was saying because they hit home and I didn't want to face the music about my messed up life. The more I listened, the more I became convicted about the need to seek God. Whether out of my alcoholism or the reality that we needed answers as to how in the world we were going to raise a child, we walked into Calvary Chapel looking for those answers. We started attending regularly since 1998 and soaked up the Word of God with a passion. We sat as students for several years before we started to serve in various ministries.</p>

	  <p>As I began to live the way that God has commanded his followers to live, I was still abusing alcohol. I was not even certain that I was saved at this point in time, but I had this terrible guilt and the feeling that I was failing God. As I look back, I know that the Holy Spirit was convicting me to live the life that would glorify, not mock, God. I was struggling and falling deeper into spiritual quicksand when, at a Sunday service, Pastor Allen mentioned that a program called Setting Captives Free was available as an online course for those struggling with alcohol, over-eating and pornography. My prayers had been answered and I was so excited that there was a discreet program that I could take that would not expose my shame. I felt as though a ton of bricks had been lifted off my chest and I enrolled the following day. Throughout the 60 day course I learned that Jesus represents the "New Wine" and that if I drink from him, I will never thirst for the "old wine" or alcohol again. I learned that I must glorify God in all things and that my life is his to use for the purpose he has for me. I was assured of my salvation through faith in Jesus Christ when I had finished this course. I had tried so many times to cut back or quit drinking and, although occasionally successful, I returned to drinking. The key is that I was not relying on Jesus Christ, but rather myself to rectify my drinking problem.</p>

	  <p>Today, I am "free indeed" and have not struggled with alcohol since finishing the course over a year ago. Unlike other programs that tell you you will always be an alcoholic, although recovering, Setting Captives Free showed me that Jesus Christ has taken this burden from me. I am not longer an alcoholic because I have been delivered from the habitual sin of drunkenness. Today, I am working on becoming a mentor in the SCF program so that I can help others find freedom in their lives. It is so encouraging to be able to see people understand the key to being free is found in the faith and mercy that Jesus Christ is ready to give. All you must do is believe and then ask!</p>
<br></br>
<br></br>
<br></br>
<br></br>
<p>back to ....<link href="../ministries/testimonies.html">Calvary Austin Testimonies</link></p>
</ministry>

</content>
