<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--

	Free Indeed Ministry- Individual Testimonies

	$Id: oe-female1.xml,v 1.3 2003/08/31 12:09:09 gregk Exp $

-->
<content title="The Lord's Table Testimony - Female">
	<ministry id="freeindeed">
	  <name>The Lord's Table Testimony - Female</name>
   
<p>I was feeling completely hopeless after failing at every "diet" known to man. I could lose weight just to regain it again and then some.  Finally, my last few attempts at dieting were complete failures resulting in zero weight loss as I rebelled when told I couldn't eat what I wanted. It made me want it that much more and I would binge before starting any diet. I didn't like counting and measuring either.</p>

<p>Then a few months ago Free Indeed (Addictions) Ministry was announced in our church. I looked up the website and read all I could, prayed about it and told a friend about it who decided to do it along with me. My plan was set and I would start the day my husband left for 2 weeks on business. I had decided not to tell him about it for fear I would only fail again. I thought this way I would have 2 weeks under my belt before I let him know what I was doing. Then on Day 8 the Lord totally convicted my heart that "Christ died for my sin of gluttony on the cross!"  I was completely broken and I called my husband to share with him what I was doing and about the Lords Table and that I now recognized my overeating for what it was "sin". I wanted to be accountable to him as well. </p>

<p>I could never envision myself as someone that could eat like a "normal" person. I can't say that it has been a bed of roses since Day 8, but for the first time in my life I can say, Christ has truly set this captive free indeed! Being reminded to put my focus back on the Lord has not only helped to discipline the way I eat now but has also helped in restoring my marriage, becoming a better wife and mother, being a better example for my children and turning my heart back toward ministry.  Praise His Holy Name!  I would also like to thank Donna, my mentor through TLT, Elizabeth, my mentor through Calvary Chapel of Austin and my friend Tracy for encouraging me and praying for me through this wonderful journey!</p> 
<br></br>
<br></br>
<br></br>
<br></br>
<p>back to ....<link href="../ministries/testimonies.html">Calvary Austin Testimonies</link></p>
</ministry>
</content>
