<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--

	Free Indeed Ministry- Individual Testimonies

	$Id: oe-mntr-fem.xml,v 1.1 2004/05/14 05:40:32 gregk Exp $

-->
<content title="The Lord's Table Testimony - Female - Mentor #1">
	<ministry id="freeindeed">
	  <name>The Lord's Table Testimony - Female - Mentor #1</name>
   
<p>I would highly recommend anyone completing The Lord's Table course to continue on into the Mentorship Course. I found the Mentorship Course to be extremely helpful in continuing my training in daily bible study, daily dependence on the Lord and accountability. I think the Course is very well laid out for training to become a mentor as well as continued daily bible study. I especially liked the way it was broken into sections, mentorship training, fasting, prayer, review, etc. Each day was divinely timed and always seemed to be 'just what I needed for that day.' I also enjoyed studying through "A Hunger for God" by John Piper and liked the way we only studied a couple of pages at a time to really ponder it and apply it. I learned so much regarding fasting that I will never view fasting the same way again. I could probably go on and on about how great I think this course is and I think everyone should do it, but I will sum it up this way... For me the 120 day Mentorship Course was good because I often think that when I hear something then "I've got it", when in fact I may have it in my head but it takes much longer for me to actually apply it. So, I needed the additional 120 days of structure, commitment, and accountability for me to see how much work the Lord was doing in my life and still had so much more work left to do. This was so much more than just a bible study and losing weigh, it turned into a renewing, strengthened relationship with my Lord and Savior. I have a new appreciation for daily time with the Lord, crying out to God in times of need and trusting in His sovereignty rather than my own abilities.</p>


<br></br>
<br></br>
<br></br>
<br></br>
<p>back to ....<link href="../ministries/testimonies.html">Calvary Austin Testimonies</link></p>
</ministry>
</content>
