<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--

	Free Indeed Ministry- Pure Freedom Testimonies

	$Id: pf-male2.xml,v 1.1 2003/11/24 04:53:00 gregk Exp $

-->
<content title="Pure Freedom Testimony - Male">
	<ministry id="freeindeed">
	  <name>Pure Freedom Testimony - Male</name>
	  <p>I am a man who has lived a life of sexual sin. I was first introduced to pornography in middle school by my step-fathers' comic books. They portrayed characters doing drugs and having sex. That begun the arousal of the sin within me.  My freshman year I found a stack of magazines in the basement of our rental house. That is where masturbation kicked into high gear. All of my relationships in high school were either based on sex or died off quickly. I had a desire to be wanted, and sex was how they would show me they wanted me. The spiral continued downward as I was involved in drugs and strip clubs in my 20s. </p>
        <p>At the age of 30, I came to the Lord. I was feeling that hole in my heart and seeking. I  got married immediately after becoming a Christian to a woman I had been having pre-martial sex with. the relationship was so devastating that sex became a horrible experience for me. That marriage ended. The hunt for porn began again.</p>
        <p>One day, I couldn't take it anymore. I begged the Lord to cleanse me. He began His work that day. He waited for me to release it to Him. I actually started this course two years later. I  thought the Lord had already cleaned me out. This course was just to double check. I was not happy with what I found. God still had some work to do in me. I am cleaner than I have ever been. I am re-married to a woman that I honored until our wedding. We have the most beautiful relationship; more wonderful than I could have imagined. She is helping me see what a truly God-based sexual relationship with our wives is all about. I have never known anything so special and beautiful.</p>
      <p>I praise the Lord that He has done a great work in me. I am now excited to serve Him as a pure and healthy man that honors Him with my every thought, action and word.</p>
      <p> back to ...<link href="../ministries/testimonies.html">Calvary Austin Testimonies</link></p>
   </ministry>
</content>
