<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- 
        Baptism and Picnic 2003 

	$Id: baptism2003.xml,v 1.1 2003/05/20 22:09:38 javajames27 Exp $
		
-->
<content title="Calvary Austin's Baptism and Picnic 2003">
     <heading>Calvary Austin's Baptism and Picnic 2003</heading>
	<p>Saturday June 21st - 12:00pm-4:30pm. 
	@ Emma Long Park (please include link to maps quest)
	Emma Long Park charges $8.00 per car load. Car pooling is recommended.</p>
	<p>Lunch starts at noon. Sign up at the events center for catered BB-Q. 
	The park is also equipped with BBQ grills if you would rather cook your own.</p>
	<p>Baptism starts at 3:00pm. </p>
	<heading>What We Believe About Baptism</heading>
	<p>Jesus Christ instituted two ordinances in the church - communion and water baptism.  While neither one can save you, they are not optional; we are commanded by the Lord to do both.  Please look up and read the following scriptures: Matthew 28:19; Mark 16:16; Acts 2:38; 10:48; 22:16; Romans 6:3; Galatians 3:27; and Colossians 2:12.</p>
	<p>Here are some guidelines concerning your baptism at Calvary:</p>
	<list>
		<item>Baptism is for believers only.  A person should be born again, trusting Jesus Christ for salvation before they are baptized.</item>
		<item>It is permissible for any person who has accepted Christ to be baptized.  However children must have accepted Christ and understand enough of water baptism to make it meaningful for them.  We do not practice "Infant Baptism."  (You may wish to contact the church office regarding "Baby Dedication.")
</item>
		<item>Baptism is by full-immersion unless that is not possible.  We baptize one at a time, backward from the standing position as a symbol that the old man is dead and that they are being buried with Christ, then raised again in newness of life.</item>
		<item>It is permissible (and encouraged) to be re-baptized if you were too young the first time and did not understand the full significance.  It is also permissible (though not necessary) to be re-baptized if you have come back to the Lord as an act of rededication.</item>
		<item>We encourage you to invite family and friends (especially unbelievers) to witness your baptism.  This is a tremendous testimony to them.</item>
		<item> REGARDING DRESS: you may wear shorts or a bathing suit but for the baptism we ask that men and women also wear a t-shirt.  Please honor the Lord and be considerate of others.  Thank you!</item>
	</list>
	<p>If you have any questions, please call the church office (719-4667).  May the Lord bless you as you take this step of obedience!</p>
</content>
