<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- 
        VBS Day Camp

	$Id: vbsdaycamp2003.xml,v 1.1 2003/05/27 22:36:26 javajames27 Exp $
		
-->
<content title="V.B.S. Day Camp">
     <heading>Vacation Bible School Day Camp</heading>
	<subheading>June 23rd-27th</subheading>

	<heading>What Is VBS Day Camp?</heading>
	<p>VBS is a week long day camp designed for school-aged children who have not yet completed fifth grade.  Activities center on learning about Jesus, exploring the Bible, and having lots of fun!  This year's VBS theme is Diving for Treasure at Agape Reef.  All of the Bible lessons involve fish or aspects of God's great love!  Your kids will be Diving into an ocean of fun at the bottom of the sea filled with treasures about God to explore.  Songs and Bible verses go along with the theme, as well as supporting activities.  This is a great way for your kids to have a blast in a safe and fun environment this summer.  They will enjoy meeting new kids, all the exciting elements of VBS and they won't stop talking at night about their adventures under the deep blue sea at Calvary Austin VBS Day Camp!</p>

<heading>When Is VBS?</heading>
<p>Monday, June 23 through Friday, June 27.  Activities each day begin at 9:00 a.m. and end at 4:00 p.m.  Extended child care is available from 8:00 a.m. to 9:00 a.m. and from 4:00 p.m. until 5:30 p.m., for those parents who work full-time.</p>

<heading>Is There a Cost?</heading>
<p>Yes, this year there is a cost of just $10.00 for the whole week. However, we do not want this fee to prevent any children from participating, so if the fee presents a hardship to any parents, several scholarships will be provided.  Simply circle the "yes" on the registration form to request a scholarship.</p>
<p>There is also a $25.00 fee associated with providing extended morning or evening daycare.  No scholarships are available for this service.</p>

<heading>Who Can Attend?</heading>
<p>All children entering kindergarten this year and who have not yet completed fifth grade.</p>

<heading>What Takes Place At VBS?</heading>

<p>Morning:</p>
<list ordered="true">
	<item>Worship and Opening skit</item>
	<item>Bible Study</item>
	<item>Crafts</item>
	<item>Snacks</item>
	<item>Games</item>
	<item>Prayer time</item>
	<item>Memory work</item>
</list>
<p>Afternoon Activities:</p>
<list ordered="true">
	<item>Story time</item>
	<item>Kid's drama</item>
	<item>Playscape or games</item>
	<item>Crafts</item>
	<item>Snacks</item>
	<item>Special Activity</item>
</list>

<heading>Reard Shopping</heading>
<p>Kids will get "pearls" for bringing or doing various things.  The pearls can be traded in at the Dive Shop for small prizes.</p>

<heading>VBS Daily Theme</heading>
<p>Monday-Bring a picture of a fish.  We'll arrange all fish and display them in a collage. Tuesday-Wear your VBS T-shirt.  They will be handed out on Monday. Wednesday-Bring a wrapped Secret Diver Gift.  A VBS reminder note will give details. Thursday-Wear something "Fishy." Friday-Wear your group color.  A VBS reminder note will give details.</p>

<heading>What Does My Child Need To Bring To VBS?</heading>
<list ordered="true">
	<item>A sack lunch each day.</item>
	<item>Pouch, purse, baggy or small bag marked clearly with name for your child's "pearls."</item>
</list>

<heading>Parent's Program?</heading>
<p>Yes, 4:00 p.m. Friday, June 27.  There will be a brief assembly as well as an exciting open house for the kids to show off their "stuff" and meet the teachers and counselors.</p>

<heading>How Can My Family Participate?</heading>
<p>Children sign up:</p>
<list ordered="true">
	<item>Calvary Austin Event Center during service times.</item>
	<item>Calvary Chapel Administration office during church office hours</item>
	<item>By Phone:  VBS Coordinator, Kerry Schroeder-219-7028; or church office-719-4667</item>
</list>

<p>Adult Participation:</p>
<list ordered="true">
	<item>We welcome your help in preparation work.  Call Kerry @ 219-7028.</item>
	<item>Plan ahead for daily themes so that your children can participate in them and earn 	"pearls."</item>
	<item>Prayer, prayer and more prayer!  We need it.  Pray for the staff and children daily, that we 	honor Jesus in all we say and do.</item>
</list>
	
</content>
