<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<content title="Pastor Allen's Blog">
  <blog name="Pastor Allen">
    <entry date="Feb 13, 2003">
      <p>Only six days until Vision Night.  The thing the Lord has put on my heart is to talk about being a two-four-two church.
    </p>
    <p>Acts 2:42 (NKJV)</p>
    
    <p>42And they continued steadfastly in the apostles' doctrine and fellowship, in the breaking of bread, and in prayers. </p>
    <p>When we talk about our vision to win, equip, and send, we understand equipping as worship, discipleship, and  fellowship.  That's what being a two-four-two church is all about.</p>
    <p>Worship?  That's "breaking bread" and "prayers".</p>
    <p>Discipleship? That's "apostle's doctrine".</p>
    <p>Fellowship? That's "fellowship".</p>
    <p>As announced, my presentation will include a building update.  I plan to be direct in addressing our financial  situation. On the one hand, it would be crass to talk money without setting the spiritual context.  On the other hand, it would be  cruel to talk building without acknowledging that we're in a recession, people are getting laid off, and times are tough for all of us  - including churches.</p>
    <p>The most important thing I plan to say is that for the next four Wednesdays - starting February 26 - we are going to  STOP and SEEK the Lord.  I don't know how to explain the depth of feeling that Andrea and I have about this other than to say  we're as sure about this as we were about coming to Austin 11-plus years ago.  These four mid-week services will be very much  like afterglows.  We will worship and wait on the Lord.  We will pray for personal renewal and church-wide revival.  We will pray  for new vision and passion.  We will ask God to open the windows of heaven and provide the resources we need.  We will ask  God to give us Austin.</p>
    <p>Andrea and I want to have hearts that say, "God speak to ME.  Change ME.  Do a new work in ME." We want you to  have hearts that say that, too.  Be open to what God wants to do.  Listen as He speaks to you.  He WILL speak to you! </p>
    <p>Two passages the Lord has put on my heart . . .</p>
    <p>Hosea 10:12 (NLT)</p>
    <p>12I said, "Plant the good seeds of righteousness, and you will harvest a crop of my love. Plow up the hard ground of  your hearts, for now is the time to seek the LORD, that he may come and shower righteousness upon you.'</p>
    <p>Hebrews 12:25-27 (TMNT)</p>
    <p>So don't turn a deaf ear to these gracious words. If those who ignored earthly warnings didn't get away with it, what  will happen to us if we turn our backs on heavenly warnings? His voice that time shook the earth to its foundations; this  time—he's told us this quite plainly—he'll also rock the heavens: "One last shaking, from top to bottom, stem to stern." The  phrase "one last shaking" means a thorough housecleaning, getting rid of all the historical and religious junk so that the  unshakable essentials stand clear and uncluttered.</p>
    <p>With great anticipation,<br/><br/>Allen</p>
  </entry>
  <entry date="Feb 26, 2003">
    <p>In answer to a question, just a quick note about fasting.  The thought was to consider fasting on Stop and Seek  Wednesdays.  It doesn't matter if it's one, two, or three meals.  The idea is to spend that time seeking the Lord and preparing  one's heart.  This just to give you ideas and to help you feel free to do whatever the Lord leads.</p>
    <p>The focus tonight will be on confession.  We'll open with a short worship set.  Afterward, following the example of  Nehemiah 9, we will continue with teaching followed by confession followed by worship.  I have no idea what to expect on the  heels of the ice storm.  Remember "faith . . . is the evidence of things not seen" (Heb 11:1).  God is going to do something  special over these four weeks.</p>
    <p>Allen</p>
  </entry>
  <entry date="Feb 27, 20003">
    <p>God DID do something special last night!  I sensed this only in part as the service progressed but based on what  several people have shared with me, it was high-impact.  In our lives this week, may we be more sensitive to the Holy Spirit.   May we be quick to confess sin to God and to one another.  May we exude joy in all we do.</p>
    <p>Psalm 51:12 (NKJV)</p>
    <p>12    Restore to me the joy of Your salvation,<br/>And uphold me by Your generous Spirit.</p>
    <p>Allen</p>
  </entry>
  <entry date="Mar 05, 2003">
    <p>The focus tonight will be on supplication.  We'll open with a short worship set, announcements, and another short  worship set.  I'm going to give people an opportunity to share a short testimony about answered prayer in their life.  Then as  David leads the church in worship, we're going to give people an opportunity to receive prayer.  Last week was real special and  this week will be, too.</p>
    <p>Allen</p>
  </entry>
  <entry date="Mar 12, 2003">
    <p>Tonight's focus will be on intercession.  After a short worship set, we'll get in small groups of three or four and pray  conversationally for our country, our city, and our church.  We'll close with more worship and corporate prayer.  In some ways,  tonight may be the most powerful yet as prayers are offered up all over the auditorium.  Can't wait to see what God is going to  do!</p>
    <p>Allen</p>
  </entry>
  <entry date="Mar 13, 2003">
    <p>Last night was the third of four "Stop and Seek" Wednesdays and it was very cool.  It was amazing to hear prayers being offered up all over the auditorium.  March 19 the focus will be on adoration.  There will be lots of praise and worship.  Even conversational prayer will be directed in a very worshipful way.   </p>
    <p>If you've attended one or more "Stop and Seek" Wednesdays, drop us an email letting us know how God has spoken to, changed, or done a new work in you.   What has He said?  How have you changed?  What new work has He done? </p>
    <p>Allen</p>
  </entry>
  <entry date="Mar 19, 2003">
    <p>We're just a couple hours from our mid-week service and from zero hour in Iraq.  The plan at Calvary is to go forward with our "Stop and Seek" grand finale.  If you're able to join us tonight, read Psalm 2 and consider God's ultimatum to the nations in verses 10-12.  Our planned theme of adoration fits perfectly as we recognize God's sovereignty.  Watch for updates throughout the week as we keep you current regarding plans for special weekend services!</p>
    <p>Allen</p>
  </entry>
  <entry date="Mar 21, 2003">
    <p>Not long after our service ended Wednesday, the President announced that the war in Iraq had begun.  With that in mind, I'm preparing a message for Sunday entitled "What the Bible Says about War."  Why is there war?  When is it right to fight?  Where is the prospect for peace?  People have questions.  The Bible has answers.  Invite a family member or friend  and join us Sunday at 8:00, 9:45, or 11:30 a.m.</p>
    <p>Allen</p>
  </entry>
  <entry date="Mar 26, 2003">
    <p>What's your take on the war?  Last weekend in Chicago anti-war activists squared off against those who support the President and our troops.  The activists shouted, "Killers!"  The supporters shouted back, "Idiots!"  Even in churches there are those who prefer - in the words of hymn writer Charles Wesley - "Gentle Jesus, meek and mild" and those who prefer G.I. Jesus!  What does the Bible say about war?</p>
    <p>The Bible tells us why there is war.  In James 4:1-2a, we discover that war is the result of selfishness. Certainly that was the motive behind Iraq's invasion of Kuwait 12 years ago.  It's interesting that while Iraqis suffer, Saddam Hussein has a personal fortune estimated by Forbes at $2 billion.</p>
    <p>The Bible also tells us when it's right to fight.  In Romans 13:4, we learn that God has given government the authority to protect it citizens - including authority to take life.  Compare 1 Peter 2:13-14 and I think you have a foundation for just war using just means to accomplish a just end.</p>
    <p>Finally the Bible tells us where the prospect for peace is.  In Isaiah 2:4, we see that there won't be peace until the Prince of Peace, Jesus Christ, comes again.  Those who have a relationship with Christ have peace with God now.  As a result, they have peace within.  And for that reason they can have peace with others.</p>
    <p>Want to know more? Explore our <link href="../media/index.html">media section</link> where you can watch Sunday's service [<link href="http://www.calvarychapel.org/austin/video/sunday.ram">Video</link> | <link href="http://www.calvarychapel.org/austin/audio/topicmessage/war.ram">Audio</link>] in its entirety!</p>
    <p>Allen</p>
  </entry>
  <entry date="Apr 17, 2003">
    <p>Last year the Gallup Organization reported that over one fourth of those who seldom go to church say they will attend on Easter.  That's a good thing!  But beneath the smiles and the "Sunday best," people feel guilty.  And lonely.  And fearful.  With that in mind, I've prepared a special message for Sunday entitled "Easter Changes Everything."  I'd like for us to see together how Easter changes our past.  How Easter changes our present.  How Easter changes our future.  Grab a friend and join us for one of our three morning services.  In fact, Sunday is shaping up to be a beautiful day in Central Texas. Why not come early or stay after and enjoy a hot drink on the deck at our coffee bar, Coffee Creator?  We look forward to meeting you Sunday! </p>
    <p>Allen</p>
  </entry>
  <entry date="May 20, 2003">
    <p>You doubt that a weather balloon explains what happened near Roswell, NM.  Not only do you doubt the Warren Report, you’re convinced J.F.K. is still alive!  You doubt the lunar landing ever happened.  Why no crater?  Where are the stars?  What about the light anomalies?  You’re frequently found posting in the X-Files Forum.  You believe "The Matrix" is real!  Okay, so you’re not a conspiracy buff.  But you have to admit that when it comes to your faith, every now and then, you experience doubt.  Check out the archived message <link href="http://www.calvarychapel.org/austin/audio/42-luk/42-luk-07-11.ram">"What to Do with Your Doubt"</link> or, better yet, join us Sunday for another faith-building message from God’s Word.
</p>
    <p>Allen</p>
  </entry>
  <entry date="Aug 28, 2003">
   <p>Prayer. Polling has shown that 9 in 10 Americans pray at one time or another. Yet ask the average churchgoer about their prayer life and you're likely to discover that they're less than satisfied. Why is that? It's certainly not a lack of resources. A recent visit to amazon.com yielded more than 17,000 titles on prayer! Maybe what we need is to get back to basics. Sunday we begin a four-week series on prayer entitled "Connecting with God" We'll study verse-by-verse through Luke 11:1-13 spending weeks two and three on the so-called "Lord's Prayer". See you Sunday!
</p>
	<p>Allen</p>
     </entry>
  <entry date="Sep 05, 2003">
   <p>Is prayer caught or taught?  Both!  The disciples caught prayer from Jesus.  They saw that He wasn't too busy to pray.  He was too busy not to!  Now they wanted to be taught prayer by Jesus.  In answer to their request, Jesus gave them the so-called "Lord's Prayer".  There are only 59 words in Luke's version (NKJV) and it takes less than a minute to recite.  But these are six power-packed sentences.  Sunday is week two in a four-week series on prayer entitled "Connecting with God."  This Sunday we'll unpack the first three sentences dealing with God's glory.  Next Sunday we'll unpack the last three sentences dealing with our good.  Finally, in week four, we'll examine the problem of unanswered prayer and learn the secret to answered prayer.
   </p>
	<p>Allen</p>
   </entry>
  <entry date="September 12, 2003">
    <p>It's interesting that the so-called "Lord's Prayer" was given in response to the request, "Lord, teach us <strong>to pray</strong>" not, "Lord, teach us <strong>a prayer</strong>."  Interesting because more people <strong>say</strong> the Lord's Prayer than <strong>pray</strong> the Lord's prayer.  What's the difference?  To <strong>say</strong> the Lord's Prayer is to recite it with heart and mind disengaged.  What Jesus meant when he warned against "vain repetitions" (Mt 6:7).  To <strong>pray</strong> the Lord's Prayer is to take it as a template and pattern our prayers after it.  Sunday is week three in a four-week series on prayer entitled "Connecting with God."  Last Sunday we unpacked the first three sentences of the Lord's Prayer dealing with God's glory.  This Sunday we'll unpack the last three sentences dealing with our good.  Next Sunday, in week four, we'll examine the problem of <strong>un</strong>answered prayer and learn the secret to <strong>answered</strong> prayer.
   </p>
	<p>Allen</p>
   </entry>
  <entry date="Sep 18, 2003">
   <p>Why do some prayers seemingly go unanswered?  In reality, there is no
such thing as "unanswered prayer."  God always answers prayer.  He says
yes, no, or wait.  We love it when He says yes.  We hate it when He says
no.  We really hate it when He says wait!  No and wait are what we refer
to as "unanswered prayer."  Sunday is the last in a four-week series
entitled "Connecting with God."  Check out the first three messages here
on our web site and join us Sunday as we examine the problem of
unanswered prayer and learn the secret to answered prayer.
    </p>
	<p>Allen</p>
   </entry>
  <entry date="Nov 5, 2003">
     <p>The 2003 Mid-South Pastors and Leaders Conference begins tomorrow.  Close to 200 people representing 35 churches in five states will gather at Calvary Austin to rediscover the need for praying leaders.  Just a reminder that the evening sessions are open to everyone and begin at 7 p.m. (not 7:30 as announced Sunday).  Sandy Adams (Calvary Chapel Stone Mountain near Atlanta) speaks Thursday and Malcolm Wild (Calvary Chapel Merritt Island in FL) speaks Friday.   Please note there is no childcare but there is a "Nursing Mothers Room" as well as a "New Parents Room" where parents with infants and toddlers can sit comfortably and watch the session on two video screens.  Hope to see you there! </p>
	<p>Allen</p>
   </entry>
  <entry date="Dec 12, 2003">
     <p>Two words. Trista and Ryan. Trista went from runner-up on "The Bachelor" to the star of the "The Bachelorette", where she chose Ryan on the show's finale, which aired in February. Wednesday night's special "Trista and Ryan's Wedding" was seen by one in 10 Americans giving ABC the lead for the night in prime time.</p>
	  <p>What if they had reality-TV in New Testament times?  What if instead of Trista and Ryan we had Mary and Joseph?  Join us December 14 and 21 for the two-part series, Reality Christmas.  Sunday, December 14, it's Mary as "The Bachelorette."  Sunday, December 21, it's Joe as "The Bachelor."</p>
	<p>Allen</p>
   </entry>
  <entry date="Dec 23, 2003">
     <p>When our daughter was born, my wife and I had chosen a first name for her but were stuck on a middle name. We wanted her to have an A-letter middle name so that she would have the same initials (though in a different order) that we did. Problem is we liked a name that started with an E. In the end, we came up with an alternative speeling so that the E-letter name started with a A. No one is sure how to pronounce it but her monogramis safe!</p>
	  <p>Mary and Joseph had no such problems because an angel told them what to name their Son. Join us for Christmas Eve at Calvary and find out what's so significant about the name <italics>Jesus</italics>. The hour-long service begins Wednesday, December 24, at 7 p.m. and includes Christmas music, drama, a special message, and a candlelight grand finale. No childcare will be provided as the entire family is invited into the auditorium for this celebration</p>
	<p>Allen</p>
   </entry>
  <entry date="Dec 26, 2003">
     <p>If you're like me, you love New Year's because it gives you an opportunity to review where you've been and to reevaluate where your're going. About this time last year, our church staff met to do a lttle goal setting. We each put a copy of our goals in a shared evenlope and sealed it like a time capsule. It will be fun to break the seal and celebrate all that was accomplished.</p>
    <p>What was 2003 like for you? What are your goals for 2004? Join us December 28 and January 4 for the two-part series, <italics>Turn It up a Notch.</italics> Sunday, December 28, corporate trainer Andy Neillie will speak about <italics>personal</italics> growth based on Luke 2:52. Sunday, January 4, our Pastor of Discipleship, Bunjee Garrett, will speak on <italics>ministry</italics> growth as we roll out CDP - the all new Calvary Discipleship Program. (By the way, Sunday, January 11, I will resume our series in Luke with a message about humility!)</p>
	<p>Allen</p>
   </entry>
  <entry date="Dec 30, 2003">
     <p>The dollar has experienced a series of record lows against the euro this month. The death toll following the Iran quake has risen to 28,000 today. The terror threat alert level is at orange - second highest on the five-tiered, color-coded scale - for at least the rest of the week. Do you ever wonder how these and other current events might fit into what the Bible says about the end times and the return of Christ?</p>
    <p>Join us Wednesday from 7-9 p.m. for New Year's Eve at Calvary. I'll be speaking about Bible prophecy and current events. We've planned a special celebration for the kids, too. For information, click on the banner below. Hope to see you there! </p>
	<p>Allen</p>
   </entry>
  <entry date="Jan 29, 2004">
     <p>3-2-1 ....</p>
     <p>A <strong>countdown?</strong> Yes! We're counting the days-three as of today-before 2/1. But 3-2-1 is more than a countdown. A <strong>launch?</strong> Yes! We're launching a two-service format that combines three-service resources with the start times you liked best. But 3-2-1 is more than a launch. It's an <strong>event!</strong> Join us Sunday at 9:30 or 11:30 a.m. and see what's new at Calvary.</p>
	<p>Allen</p>
   </entry>
  <entry date="Feb 25, 2004">
     <p>What a week for worship! Our annual worship conference starts tomorrow but worship starts tonight and continues through Sunday. Tonight Art Murillo and Sunday Drivers lead worship. Sunday, Holland Davis leads worship. Grab somebody, hit Coffee Creator on your way in, and worship loud!</p>
	<p>Allen</p>
   </entry>
  <entry date="March 3, 2004">
     <p>It's a first: <italics>Vision Sunday</italics> at Calvary. We've done a couple vision nights but never before have we set aside entire Sunday services to share our purpose and to vision-cast. You <italics>have</italics> to come! You just <italics>have to!</italics> Don't just plan to <italics>come,</italics> plan to <italics>come early</italics>. We're going to celebrate God's <italics>faithfulness</italics> and all the life-change that's taken place at Calvary over the last year. Then we're going to peek into the <italics>future</italics> and own our God-given vision. Don't forget that we'll also ordain the newest pastors added to our staff. You <italics>can't</italics> miss it. You just <italics>can't!</italics></p>
	<p>Allen</p>
   </entry>
  <entry date="March 9, 2004">
     <p>Vision Sunday was a great success! With around 1.000 in attendance, we were able to communicate our God-given purpose and do some vision-casting. Sunday, April 4, is kick-off Sunday for <strong>Building Momentum</strong> - our plan to meet critical space needs as Calvary Austin continues to grow. If you weren't here Sunday and didn't get a <strong>Building Momentum Prayer Guide,</strong> be sure to pick one up this week and commit yourself to praying with us throughout the month of March. Monday's opening devotional was cool as it suggested we imagine what it would be like if there were more Christians in Austin. I took it a step further. What if the facility we are going to build was like a spiritual ground zero with ridiculous numbers of people getting saved in the surrounding area? You get the idea ....</p>
	<p>Allen</p>
   </entry>
  <entry date="March 16, 2004">
     <p>Momentum is building for <strong>Building Momentum</strong> - our plan to meet critical space needs as Calvary Austin continues to grow. Kick-off Sunday is April 4 but you might think of the month of March as a pre-event. It began with Vision Sunday March 7 and continues with a special emphasis on prayer. We're distributed hundreds of <strong>Building Momentum Prayer Guides</strong> to people praying with us for God's special blessing on our church. This Wednesday and next we have transformed our mid-week service into a church-wide prayer meeting. Called "Stop &amp; Seek" Wednesdays, what happens March 17 and 24 will be even more critical than pit stops at a NASCAR race. The margin of victory in Sunday's Golden Corral 500 was 4.584 seconds. Races can be won or lost in the pit! Come join the <strong>Building Momentum</strong> crew Wednesday at 7 p.m. </p>
	<p>Allen</p>
   </entry>
  <entry date="March 18, 2004">
     <p>Last night's <strong>Building Momentum</strong> pre-event was really special. It was the first of two mid-week services with a special prayer emphasis. David and the worship team opened with a couple songs followed by a very cool <strong>Building Momentum</strong> graphic. After a giving a short summary of <italics>Vision Sunday</italics> and a calendar of events for <strong>Building Momentum</strong>, I  spoke for several minutes about prayer. James 4:2 says, "you do not have because you do not ask." That inspires me to ask! For the first time, I gave some specifics as to the magnitude of the project. Then we had a time of conversational prayer thanking God for His power, protection, and provision in our lives. After David led a three-song worship set, we broke into small groups and prayed asking God to bless our church spiritually, numerically, and financially. Then we closed with another three-song set.</p>
     <p>Sunday we come to the place in Luke where the movie <italics>The Passion of the Christ</italics> begins. We'll look together at Jesus' arrest in the garden and Peter's denial. "DisPassion" is the title of the message. From Peter's experience, we learn five things we can do to keep from becoming dispassionate about Christ. Last week when we gave people an opportunity to come forward to receive - or recommit their life to  - Christ, 26 people responded! My point? Don't miss what God wants to do in you this Sunday at church. And bring someone you care about!</p>
	<p>Allen</p>
   </entry>
  <entry date="March 25, 2004">
     <p>The final <strong>Building Momentum</strong> pre-event was, if possible, the best. It was the second of two mid-week services with a special prayer emphasis both of which followed <italics>Vision Sunday</italics>. David and the worship team opened with a three-song set followed by a time of directed silent prayer using I Corinthinans 11:23 as a guide. We then had a creative communion celebration. David led us in worship while pairs of Elders and Pastors were available for those with prayer needs. The bread and juice were on two tables at the front and worshipers were invited to partake as they felt led. That was followed by a time of conversational prayer that included prayers for Easter weekend and <strong>Building Momentum.</strong></p>
     <p>In case you don't know, <strong>Building Momentum</strong> is our plan to meet critical space needs as Calvary Austin continues to grow. Very soon information will be available at the link below. The campaign begins not this Sunday but next (April 4). This week we'll prepare our hearts for Easter weekend with a look at the crucifixion of Christ and His seven sayings from the cross.</p> 
	<p>Allen</p>
   </entry>

  <entry date="March 31, 2004">
     <p>This weekend is another big <italics>first Sunday</italics> at Calvary Austin. The first Sunday in February was <italics>3-2-1</italics>. That's the weekend we put three-service resources into a two-service format. The results have been outstanding! The first Sunday in March was <italics>Vision Sunday</italics>. That's the weekend we talked about our purpose as a church and did a little vision-casting. It was our best attended weekend ever with the exception of Easter</p>
	<p>This Sunday April 4, the first Sunday in April, is Kick-Off Sunday for <strong>Building Momentum</strong> - our plan to meet critical space needs as Calvary Austin continues to grow. For the next several weeks, we will take a small portion of our weekend services to communicate with you regarding <strong>Building Momentum.</strong> This Sunday we're going to show you a virtual tour of our new facility and tell you more about what to expect over the next several weeks.</p>
     <p>I am very excited about the message series we've planned. For the last couple years I've wanted to do a series of messages from the book of Nehemiah. The series will be entitled (drum roll here) <strong>Building Momentum!</strong> It's about building momentum in every part of our lives: as individuals, as families, and as a church. Join us this weekend for an incredible time of worship, the virtual tour, and a Bible study from Nehemiah 1 as we kick off <strong>Building Momentum</strong>.</p> 
	<p>Allen</p>
   </entry>
  <entry date="April 6, 2004">
     <p>Kick-Off Sunday for <strong>Building Momentum</strong> - our plan to meet critical space needs as Calvary Austin continues to grow - was a blast! We went from worship right into video filmed on location introducing a virtual tour of our proposed facility at Wells Branch Parkway and Heatherwilde. Afterward I dialogued onstage with two key staff members about some of the details(i.e. a 1,000-seat auditorium, 660 parking spaces, state-of-the art youth and children's space) and the calendar of events for <strong>Building Momentum.</strong></p>
	<p>But <strong>Building Momentum</strong> is more than a building project. It's a message series! From the Old Testament story about Nehemiah, we're learning how to be momentum-builders - MBs for short - in every area of our lives: as individuals, as families, and as a church. We learned Sunday that momentum begins with seeing, sensing, and seeking what God wants us to do. Sunday, April 18, we will learn how to go from <italics>praying</italics> about what <italics>is</italics> to <italics>planning</italics> for what <italics>could be.</italics></p>
	<p> But first we celebrate Easter! I'll update my blog with more about that in a day or two. In the meantime, check out <link href="http://www.easterservice.com">www.easterservice.com!</link></p>
	<p>Allen</p>
   </entry>
  <entry date="April 9, 2004">
     <p>What a weekend!</p>
     <p><strong>Friday morning</strong> between 7 and 8 a.m. catch the Calvary Austin worship team <link href="http://www.calvaryaustinmusic.org">(www.calvaryaustinmusic.org)</link> on Fox 7 News in the Morning.<link href="http://www.fox7news.com">(www.fox7news.com)</link> They will be performing songs from their new CD <italics>I Will</italics> as well promoting our weekend services.</p>
	<p><strong>Friday night</strong> at 7 p.m., Calvary Austin presents the live multi-media performance <italics>No Appeal</italics>. <italics>No Appeal</italics> combines drama, live music, and video to reach the hearts of audience members. I'll follow that with a brief message tying it all together. As alvays our coffee bar, Coffee Creator, will be open before and after the performance so you can connect with people like you!</p>
	<p><strong>Sunday morning</strong> at 9:30 a.m. and again at 11:30 a.m., it's Easter Sunday at Calvary Austin! With worship by the Calvary Austin worship team and special music by Danny Oertli <link href="http://www.dannyoertli.com">(www.dannyoertli.com)</link>, it's sure to be an inspiring service! I'll be sharing a message about the death and resurrection of Christ. For information, visit <link href="http://wwww.easterservice.com">www.easterservice.com</link>!</p>
   </entry>
</blog>
</content>
