<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<content title="Pastor Allen's Blog">
  <blog name="Pastor Allen">
    <entry date="Feb 13, 2003">
      <p>Only six days until Vision Night.  The thing the Lord has put on my heart is to talk about being a two-four-two church.
    </p>
    <p>Acts 2:42 (NKJV)</p>
    
    <p>42And they continued steadfastly in the apostles' doctrine and fellowship, in the breaking of bread, and in prayers. </p>
    <p>When we talk about our vision to win, equip, and send, we understand equipping as worship, discipleship, and  fellowship.  That's what being a two-four-two church is all about.</p>
    <p>Worship?  That's "breaking bread" and "prayers".</p>
    <p>Discipleship? That's "apostle's doctrine".</p>
    <p>Fellowship? That's "fellowship".</p>
    <p>As announced, my presentation will include a building update.  I plan to be direct in addressing our financial  situation. On the one hand, it would be crass to talk money without setting the spiritual context.  On the other hand, it would be  cruel to talk building without acknowledging that we're in a recession, people are getting laid off, and times are tough for all of us  - including churches.</p>
    <p>The most important thing I plan to say is that for the next four Wednesdays - starting February 26 - we are going to  STOP and SEEK the Lord.  I don't know how to explain the depth of feeling that Andrea and I have about this other than to say  we're as sure about this as we were about coming to Austin 11-plus years ago.  These four mid-week services will be very much  like afterglows.  We will worship and wait on the Lord.  We will pray for personal renewal and church-wide revival.  We will pray  for new vision and passion.  We will ask God to open the windows of heaven and provide the resources we need.  We will ask  God to give us Austin.</p>
    <p>Andrea and I want to have hearts that say, "God speak to ME.  Change ME.  Do a new work in ME." We want you to  have hearts that say that, too.  Be open to what God wants to do.  Listen as He speaks to you.  He WILL speak to you! </p>
    <p>Two passages the Lord has put on my heart . . .</p>
    <p>Hosea 10:12 (NLT)</p>
    <p>12I said, "Plant the good seeds of righteousness, and you will harvest a crop of my love. Plow up the hard ground of  your hearts, for now is the time to seek the LORD, that he may come and shower righteousness upon you.'</p>
    <p>Hebrews 12:25-27 (TMNT)</p>
    <p>So don't turn a deaf ear to these gracious words. If those who ignored earthly warnings didn't get away with it, what  will happen to us if we turn our backs on heavenly warnings? His voice that time shook the earth to its foundations; this  time—he's told us this quite plainly—he'll also rock the heavens: "One last shaking, from top to bottom, stem to stern." The  phrase "one last shaking" means a thorough housecleaning, getting rid of all the historical and religious junk so that the  unshakable essentials stand clear and uncluttered.</p>
    <p>With great anticipation,<br/><br/>Allen</p>
  </entry>
  <entry date="Feb 26, 2003">
    <p>In answer to a question, just a quick note about fasting.  The thought was to consider fasting on Stop and Seek  Wednesdays.  It doesn't matter if it's one, two, or three meals.  The idea is to spend that time seeking the Lord and preparing  one's heart.  This just to give you ideas and to help you feel free to do whatever the Lord leads.</p>
    <p>The focus tonight will be on confession.  We'll open with a short worship set.  Afterward, following the example of  Nehemiah 9, we will continue with teaching followed by confession followed by worship.  I have no idea what to expect on the  heels of the ice storm.  Remember "faith . . . is the evidence of things not seen" (Heb 11:1).  God is going to do something  special over these four weeks.</p>
    <p>Allen</p>
  </entry>
  <entry date="Feb 27, 20003">
    <p>God DID do something special last night!  I sensed this only in part as the service progressed but based on what  several people have shared with me, it was high-impact.  In our lives this week, may we be more sensitive to the Holy Spirit.   May we be quick to confess sin to God and to one another.  May we exude joy in all we do.</p>
    <p>Psalm 51:12 (NKJV)</p>
    <p>12    Restore to me the joy of Your salvation,<br/>And uphold me by Your generous Spirit.</p>
    <p>Allen</p>
  </entry>
  <entry date="Mar 05, 2003">
    <p>The focus tonight will be on supplication.  We'll open with a short worship set, announcements, and another short  worship set.  I'm going to give people an opportunity to share a short testimony about answered prayer in their life.  Then as  David leads the church in worship, we're going to give people an opportunity to receive prayer.  Last week was real special and  this week will be, too.</p>
    <p>Allen</p>
  </entry>
  <entry date="Mar 12, 2003">
    <p>Tonight's focus will be on intercession.  After a short worship set, we'll get in small groups of three or four and pray  conversationally for our country, our city, and our church.  We'll close with more worship and corporate prayer.  In some ways,  tonight may be the most powerful yet as prayers are offered up all over the auditorium.  Can't wait to see what God is going to  do!</p>
    <p>Allen</p>
  </entry>
  <entry date="March 13, 2003">
    <p>Last night was the third of four "Stop and Seek" Wednesdays and it was very cool.  It was amazing to hear prayers being offered up all over the auditorium.  March 19 the focus will be on adoration.  There will be lots of praise and worship.  Even conversational prayer will be directed in a very worshipful way.   </p>
    <p>If you've attended one or more "Stop and Seek" Wednesdays, drop us an email letting us know how God has spoken to, changed, or done a new work in you.   What has He said?  How have you changed?  What new work has He done? </p>
    <p>Allen</p>
  </entry>
  <entry date="March 19, 2003">
    <p>We're just a couple hours from our mid-week service and from zero hour in Iraq.  The plan at Calvary is to go forward with our "Stop and Seek" grand finale.  If you're able to join us tonight, read Psalm 2 and consider God's ultimatum to the nations in verses 10-12.  Our planned theme of adoration fits perfectly as we recognize God's sovereignty.  Watch for updates throughout the week as we keep you current regarding plans for special weekend services!</p>
    <p>Allen</p>
  </entry>
  <entry date="March 21, 2003">
    <p>Not long after our service ended Wednesday, the President announced that the war in Iraq had begun.  With that in mind, I'm preparing a message for Sunday entitled "What the Bible Says about War."  Why is there war?  When is it right to fight?  Where is the prospect for peace?  People have questions.  The Bible has answers.  Invite a family member or friend  and join us Sunday at 8:00, 9:45, or 11:30 a.m.</p>
    <p>Allen</p>
  </entry>
  <entry date="March 26, 2003">
    <p>What's your take on the war?  Last weekend in Chicago anti-war activists squared off against those who support the President and our troops.  The activists shouted, "Killers!"  The supporters shouted back, "Idiots!"  Even in churches there are those who prefer - in the words of hymn writer Charles Wesley - "Gentle Jesus, meek and mild" and those who prefer G.I. Jesus!  What does the Bible say about war?</p>
    <p>The Bible tells us why there is war.  In James 4:1-2a, we discover that war is the result of selfishness. Certainly that was the motive behind Iraq's invasion of Kuwait 12 years ago.  It's interesting that while Iraqis suffer, Saddam Hussein has a personal fortune estimated by Forbes at $2 billion.</p>
    <p>The Bible also tells us when it's right to fight.  In Romans 13:4, we learn that God has given government the authority to protect it citizens - including authority to take life.  Compare 1 Peter 2:13-14 and I think you have a foundation for just war using just means to accomplish a just end.</p>
    <p>Finally the Bible tells us where the prospect for peace is.  In Isaiah 2:4, we see that there won't be peace until the Prince of Peace, Jesus Christ, comes again.  Those who have a relationship with Christ have peace with God now.  As a result, they have peace within.  And for that reason they can have peace with others.</p>
    <p>Want to know more? Explore our <link href="../media/index.html">media section</link> where you can watch Sunday's service [<link href="http://www.calvarychapel.org/austin/video/sunday.ram">Video</link> | <link href="http://www.calvarychapel.org/austin/audio/topicmessage/war.ram">Audio</link>] in its entirety!</p>
    <p>Allen</p>
  </entry>
  <entry date="April 17, 2003">
    <p>Last year the Gallup Organization reported that over one fourth of those who seldom go to church say they will attend on Easter.  That's a good thing!  But beneath the smiles and the "Sunday best," people feel guilty.  And lonely.  And fearful.  With that in mind, I've prepared a special message for Sunday entitled "Easter Changes Everything."  I'd like for us to see together how Easter changes our past.  How Easter changes our present.  How Easter changes our future.  Grab a friend and join us for one of our three morning services.  In fact, Sunday is shaping up to be a beautiful day in Central Texas. Why not come early or stay after and enjoy a hot drink on the deck at our coffee bar, Coffee Creator?  We look forward to meeting you Sunday! </p>
    <p>Allen</p>
  </entry>
  <entry date="May 20, 2003">
    <p>You doubt that a weather balloon explains what happened near Roswell, NM.  Not only do you doubt the Warren Report, you’re convinced J.F.K. is still alive!  You doubt the lunar landing ever happened.  Why no crater?  Where are the stars?  What about the light anomalies?  You’re frequently found posting in the X-Files Forum.  You believe "The Matrix" is real!  Okay, so you’re not a conspiracy buff.  But you have to admit that when it comes to your faith, every now and then, you experience doubt.  Check out the archived message <link href="http://www.calvarychapel.org/austin/audio/42-luk/42-luk-07-11.ram">"What to Do with Your Doubt"</link> or, better yet, join us Sunday for another faith-building message from God’s Word.
</p>
    <p>Allen</p>
  </entry>
  <entry date="August 28,2003">
   <p>Prayer. Polling has shown that 9 in 10 Americans pray at one time or another. Yet ask the average churchgoer about their prayer life and you're likely to discover that they're less than satisfied. Why is that? It's certainly not a lack of resources. A recent visit to amazon.com yielded more than 17,000 titles on prayer! Maybe what we need is to get back to basics. Sunday we begin a four-week series on prayer entitled "Connecting with God" We'll study verse-by-verse through Luke 11:1-13 spending weeks two and three on the so-called "Lord's Prayer". See you Sunday!
</p>
	<p>Allen</p>
     </entry>
  <entry date="September 5,2003">
   <p>Is prayer caught or taught?  Both!  The disciples caught prayer from Jesus.  They saw that He wasn't too busy to pray.  He was too busy not to!  Now they wanted to be taught prayer by Jesus.  In answer to their request, Jesus gave them the so-called "Lord's Prayer".  There are only 59 words in Luke's version (NKJV) and it takes less than a minute to recite.  But these are six power-packed sentences.  Sunday is week two in a four-week series on prayer entitled "Connecting with God."  This Sunday we'll unpack the first three sentences dealing with God's glory.  Next Sunday we'll unpack the last three sentences dealing with our good.  Finally, in week four, we'll examine the problem of unanswered prayer and learn the secret to answered prayer.
   </p>
	<p>Allen</p>
   </entry>
</blog>
</content>
