<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<content title="Pastor Allen's Blog">
	<blog name="Pastor Allen">
		<entry date="Feb 13, 2003">
				<p>Only six days until Vision Night.  The thing the Lord has put on my heart is to talk about being a two-four-two church.
	</p>
				<p>Acts 2:42 (NKJV)</p>
	
				<p>42And they continued steadfastly in the apostles’ doctrine and fellowship, in the breaking of bread, and in prayers.	</p>
				<p>When we talk about our vision to win, equip, and send, we understand equipping as worship, discipleship, and 	fellowship.  That’s what being a two-four-two church is all about.</p>
				<p>Worship?  That’s “breaking bread” and “prayers”.</p>
				<p>Discipleship? That’s “apostle’s doctrine”.</p>
				<p>Fellowship? That’s “fellowship”.</p>
				<p>As announced, my presentation will include a building update.  I plan to be direct in addressing our financial 	situation. On the one hand, it would be crass to talk money without setting the spiritual context.  On the other hand, it would be 	cruel to talk building without acknowledging that we’re in a recession, people are getting laid off, and times are tough for all of us 	– including churches.</p>
				<p>The most important thing I plan to say is that for the next four Wednesdays – starting February 26 – we are going to 	STOP and SEEK the Lord.  I don’t know how to explain the depth of feeling that Andrea and I have about this other than to say 	we’re as sure about this as we were about coming to Austin 11-plus years ago.  These four mid-week services will be very much 	like afterglows.  We will worship and wait on the Lord.  We will pray for personal renewal and church-wide revival.  We will pray 	for new vision and passion.  We will ask God to open the windows of heaven and provide the resources we need.  We will ask 	God to give us Austin.</p>
				<p>Andrea and I want to have hearts that say, “God speak to ME.  Change ME.  Do a new work in ME.” We want you to 	have hearts that say that, too.  Be open to what God wants to do.  Listen as He speaks to you.  He WILL speak to you! </p>
				<p>Two passages the Lord has put on my heart . . .</p>
				<p>Hosea 10:12 (NLT)</p>
				<p>12I said, ‘Plant the good seeds of righteousness, and you will harvest a crop of my love. Plow up the hard ground of 	your hearts, for now is the time to seek the LORD, that he may come and shower righteousness upon you.’</p>
				<p>Hebrews 12:25-27 (TMNT)</p>
				<p>So don’t turn a deaf ear to these gracious words. If those who ignored earthly warnings didn’t get away with it, what 	will happen to us if we turn our backs on heavenly warnings? His voice that time shook the earth to its foundations; this 	time—he’s told us this quite plainly—he’ll also rock the heavens: “One last shaking, from top to bottom, stem to stern.” The 	phrase “one last shaking” means a thorough housecleaning, getting rid of all the historical and religious junk so that the 	unshakable essentials stand clear and uncluttered.</p>
				<p>With great anticipation,<br/><br/>Allen</p>
		</entry>
		<entry date="Feb 26, 2003">
				<p>In answer to a question, just a quick note about fasting.  The thought was to consider fasting on Stop and Seek 	Wednesdays.  It doesn't matter if it's one, two, or three meals.  The idea is to spend that time seeking the Lord and preparing 	one's heart.  This just to give you ideas and to help you feel free to do whatever the Lord leads.</p>
				<p>The focus tonight will be on confession.  We'll open with a short worship set.  Afterward, following the example of 	Nehemiah 9, we will continue with teaching followed by confession followed by worship.  I have no idea what to expect on the 	heels of the ice storm.  Remember "faith . . . is the evidence of things not seen" (Heb 11:1).  God is going to do something 	special over these four weeks.</p>
				<p>Allen</p>
		</entry>
		<entry date="Feb 27, 20003">
				<p>God DID do something special last night!  I sensed this only in part as the service progressed but based on what 	several people have shared with me, it was high-impact.  In our lives this week, may we be more sensitive to the Holy Spirit.  	May we be quick to confess sin to God and to one another.  May we exude joy in all we do.</p>
				<p>Psalm 51:12 (NKJV)</p>
				<p>12    Restore to me the joy of Your salvation,<br/>And uphold me by Your generous Spirit.</p>
				<p>Allen</p>
		</entry>
		<entry date="Mar 5, 2003">
				<p>The focus tonight will be on supplication.  We'll open with a short worship set, announcements, and another short 	worship set.  I'm going to give people an opportunity to share a short testimony about answered prayer in their life.  Then as 	David leads the church in worship, we're going to give people an opportunity to receive prayer.  Last week was real special and 	this week will be, too.</p>
				<p>Allen</p>
		</entry>
		<entry date="Mar 12, 2003">
				<p>Tonight’s focus will be on intercession.  After a short worship set, we’ll get in small groups of three or four and pray 	conversationally for our country, our city, and our church.  We’ll close with more worship and corporate prayer.  In some ways, 	tonight may be the most powerful yet as prayers are offered up all over the auditorium.  Can’t wait to see what God is going to 	do!</p>
				<p>Allen</p>
		</entry>
	</blog>
</content>
